<LocalizationFile>
	<TokenList>
        <Token>
            <Index>52</Index>
            <Text>Battle-Sense</Text>
        </Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>53</Index>
            <Text>Heightened senses and an awareness of their surroundings have allowed this race to focus during combat. Projectiles fired by their weapons are reliably able to inflict 20% more damage.</Text>
        </Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>54</Index>
            <Text>Unaware</Text>
        </Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>55</Index>
            <Text>Races that evolve weak sensory organs suffer a penalty in space combat. Projectiles fired by their weapons inflict 20% less damage.</Text>
        </Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>71</Index>
             <Text>As a result of their streamlined and coordinated use of resources, efficient races earn a 25% reduction to the maintenance costs of ships and structures.</Text>
         </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>403</Index>
			<Text>Aeroponic Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>404</Index>
			<Text>Aeroponics is the use of a hydro-atomized spray to deliver nutrients to plants suspended in the air. This technique offers excellent plant growth and eliminates the need for soil while at the same time minimizing pathogen risks. +1 flat bonus to Food production, +10 storage, and +0.1 food per colonist assigned.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>405</Index>
			<Text>+2 food per turn, 10 storage</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
			<Index>406</Index>
			<Text>Biospheres</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>407</Index>
			<Text>Biospheres are special, highly adaptable living habitats. Biospheres may only be built on uninhabitable terrain. In doing so, the terrain becomes habitable and the planet gains maximum population based on the Colonists per Tile. Other buildings can thereafter be built underneath the biosphere.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
		  <Index>408</Index>
		  <Text>population cap; turns inhabitable tiles into habitable tiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>412</Index>
			<Text>Cloning Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>413</Index>
			<Text>Cloning Centers increase the population growth of a planet at a fixed rate of 0.02 per turn.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>414</Index>
			<Text>+0.02 population per turn</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>418</Index>
			<Text>Deep Core Mine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>419</Index>
			<Text>Deep Core Mines are extremely effective at rapidly extracting minerals from deep within a planet's core, but are environmentally disastrous. Adds flat rate production equal to four times a planet's mineral richness but decreases a planet's fertility by 3!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>420</Index>
			<Text> (-3) fertility on build, +production equal to 8 x richness, +50 storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>421</Index>
			<Text>Genetics Lab</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>422</Index>
			<Text>The output of this Genetics Research Facility scales with the amount of colonists dedicated to the task, providing +.2 research per assigned colonist. it also provides some extra flat food bonus to the colony</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>423</Index>
			<Text>+.2 research per assigned colonist, +1 Food per turn</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>427</Index>
			<Text>Imperial Bank</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>428</Index>
			<Text>The Imperial Bank building increases the efficiency of your planetary tax operations by 40% and increases credits per colonist by 0.25.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>429</Index>
			<Text>+50% tax revenues, +0.5 Credits Per Colonist</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>430</Index>
			<Text>Imperial Offices</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>431</Index>
			`<Text>Imperial Offices allow for the direct taxation of the citizenry, granting incomes at a rate of 0.25 credits per colonist and +10% Tax per turn.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>432</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 credits per colonist, +10% Tax</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>439</Index>
			<Text>Missile Silo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>440</Index>
			<Text>This missile silo fires long range guided anti-ship missiles for maximum planetary defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>441</Index>
			<Text>Fires 3 long range missiles into orbit</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>452</Index>
			<Text>Research Lab</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>453</Index>
			<Text>A dedicated research lab allows colonists to begin in earnest the study of their new home.  Provides a flat +0.5 per turn research bonus to any colony. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>454</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 research per turn, +0.1 research per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>455</Index>
			<Text>Rover Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>456</Index>
			<Text>Manned and automated rovers provide indispensable labor savings to fledgling colonies, increasing the production of the colony with a flat +1 production bonus and some storage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>457</Index>
			<Text>+1 production per turn, +10 storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>458</Index>
			<Text>Space Port</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>459</Index>
			<Text>A space port connects to the orbital star base above and allows for the construction of ships here using materials produced on the planet. Provides a 50% bonus to all monetary incomes earned on this planet.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>460</Index>
			<Text>+50% tax revenues, allows ship construction, aids in ship repairs, adds some storage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>470</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>471</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Farms are large complexes dedicated to the successful integration of our farming and husbandry techniques with alien soils and nutrients.  The production of this building scales with the number of farmers assigned on this planet. Provides +0.5 food per turn per assigned colonist. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>472</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 food per assigned colonist, +25 storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>473</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Mine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>474</Index>
			<Text>Xeno mines are the first real step toward's exploiting a planet's mineral deposits, creating +.75 production per colonist assigned to industrial tasks.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>475</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 production per assigned colonist, +30 storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>599</Index>
			<Text>Economic Foundations</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>637</Index>
			<Text>If we channeled highly-ionized Plasma directly from a ship reactor through a magnetized, high-pressure system, then we could spray our enemies with super-heated energy to devastating effect. Very effective against Armor but weak against shields. We also can now use similar methods to build a medium plasma cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
     	 <Index>682</Index>
     		 <Text>Increases the range of all sensors by 50%.</Text>
   		 </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>693</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Computing I</Text>
		</Token>		 
		<Token>
			<Index>917</Index>
			<Text>By creating massive shield projectors, we can envelop entire ships, including escort ships, inside a single shield bubble. The power costs are massive but our military scientists believe that we can create excellent screening ships with this technology.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
      		<Index>920</Index>
      		<Text>Combat Information Center</Text>
   		 </Token>
   		 <Token>
     		 <Index>921</Index>
      		 <Text>The combat information center consolidates all command and control functions into a single module. From here the crew can coordinate sensor data, manage damage control teams, organize shipboard defensive actions, and more. Provides ship wide bonuses to various system and small warp inhibitor bubble.</Text>
    </Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>949</Index>
			<Text>A small shield developed specifically for our fighter and corvette ships. It is weaker than our medium shield generator, but still provides increasingly important protection for small craft. </Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>996</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk2</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>997</Index>
			<Text>A medium range missile launcher on a swivel turret shooting 4 missiles per salvo. It also has the Terminal Phase system.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>998</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>999</Index>
			<Text>Medium range multi-rocket launching system. It has a terminal phase system, meaning at a certain range from the target, the missile will disable the guidance system and will greatly accelerate to avoid interception.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1000</Index>
			<Text>Tactical Nuclear Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1001</Index>
			<Text>A bomb bay that allows a ship to strike a planet with low-yield tactical nuclear bombs. The Target planet will suffer temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1002</Index>
			<Text>Med. Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1003</Index>
			<Text>Reactors are the beating hearts of spaceships.  This basic fission model provides a moderate level of power output and power storage. Explodes when destroyed. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1004</Index>
			<Text>Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1005</Index>
			<Text>Power Plants are the beating hearts of spaceships.  This basic fission model provides a moderate level of power output and power storage. Explodes when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1006</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1007</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance represents a ship's stores of munitions and explosives such as bullets, missiles, torpedoes, mines, and other special weapons.  A basic ordnance locker such as this one provides a captain with a safe and convenient place to store their munitions.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1008</Index>
			<Text>Small Ordnance</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1010</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Supply Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1011</Index>
			<Text>An ordnance supply bay allows a ship to launch resupply shuttles filled with ammunition to resupply friendly ships. Only one shuttle may be active per bay at a time. Supply shuttles can ferry 100 ordnance at a time.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1012</Index>
			<Text>Heavy-mount Phasor Array</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1013</Index>
			<Text>This heavy-mount phasor array has a fixed spinal facing and a 45 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1014</Index>
			<Text>Light Phasor Array</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1015</Index>
			<Text>Phasors are powerful and efficient directed energy weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1016</Index>
			<Text>Photon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1017</Index>
			<Text>A turret mounted photon cannon weapon, highly effective in any combat situation.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1018</Index>
			<Text>Twin Photon Cannons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1019</Index>
			<Text>Twin photon cannons mounted on a turret platform with advance cooling systems for rapid and sustained fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1020</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1021</Index>
			<Text>This weapon is best used at low speeds and close ranges. Higher speeds cause the plasma to disperse ineffectively, and the weapon is simply useless at range. But up close, it is devastating.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1022</Index>
			<Text>Large Plasteel Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1023</Index>
			<Text>Plasteel armor provides approximately 25% less protection than steel armor but does so with half of the mass</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1024</Index>
			<Text>Medium Plasteel Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1025</Index>
			<Text>Plasteel armor provides approximately 25% less protection than steel armor but does so with half of the mass</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1026</Index>
			<Text>Small Plasteel Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1027</Index>
			<Text>Plasteel armor provides approximately 25% less protection than steel armor but does so with half of the mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1028</Index>
			<Text>Polaron Cannon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1029</Index>
			<Text>A turret mounted polaron cannon weapon. Bypasses shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1030</Index>
			<Text>Twin Polaron Cannons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1031</Index>
			<Text>Twin polaron cannons mounted on a turret platform with advance cooling systems for rapid and sustained fire. Bypasses shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1032</Index>
			<Text>Power Conduit</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1033</Index>
			<Text>Carries power across a ship</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1034</Index>
			<Text>Pulse Capacitor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1035</Index>
			<Text>This is an inexpensive but bulky electromagnetic capacitor. Any ship equipped with pulse capacitors will be substantially more difficult to disable with electromagnetic pulse weaponry. They also help the ship recover faster from EMP overloads.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1036</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Torpedo Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1037</Index>
			<Text>A devastatingly powerful energy cannon. An expansion upon photon technology, this cannon fires guided energy photon projectiles that are very unlikely to be intercepted by Anti Missile weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>1049</Index>
            <Text>This large shielding generator will provide substantial protection for our ships over a much wider area than previous shields. It was designed to be used effectively on larger ships.</Text>
        </Token>
        <Token>
            <Index>1051</Index>
            <Text>This medium shield generator was developed in response to the need for stronger, less energy dependant shielding module for our ships. It requires less power than our Class I Magshields and provides much more protection, but has a slightly smaller range. </Text>
        </Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1223</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by 8% across the board. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1224</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by 12% across the board. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1225</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by 16% across the board. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>1226</Index>
			<Text>New materials reduce effective ship mass by 20% across the board. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2116</Index>
			<Text>The schematics for this building were found in the ruins on the Remnant homeworld. We believe that this device will allow us to transcend our physical forms. We won't know until we build it and turn it on.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2290</Index>
			<Text>Vertical Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2291</Index>
			<Text> (+0.1) fertility on build, +7 food per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2292</Index>
			<Text>This megastructure employs advanced agricultural techniques and robotics to create massive quantities of food</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>2249</Index>
			<Text>Flechette Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2250</Index>
			<Text>The Flechette shotgun is a close combat weapon. The rounds fired by this shotgun are designed to shatter upon impact for the greatest possible damage to lightly armored targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>2251</Index>
			<Text>Improved MRM Platforms</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Third wave! to do manually -->
		<Token>
			<Index>4000</Index>
			<Text>Raider Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4001</Index>
			<Text>These bays are slightly larger than standard ones. They store larger ships, and are more efficient at launching them.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4002</Index>
			<Text>Quantanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4003</Index>
			<Text>Quantanium Armor plating has a density 10 times that of steel, making it incredibly strong but also incredibly massive. It is expensive to produce.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4004</Index>
			<Text>Change audio, video, and gameplay settings. Changes do not require restart.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4005</Index>
			<Text>PAUSED</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4006</Index>
			<Text>Rule Options</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4007</Index>
			<Text>In-System FTL Speed Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4008</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Gravity Wells</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4009</Index>
			<Text>The Hyperspace Flux has abated \nShips may once again warp freely</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4010</Index>
			<Text>A massive hyperspace flux is inhibiting warp travel throughout the galaxy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4011</Index>
			<!-- "planet name has ..."-->
			<Text> has suddenly shifted in its orbit, resulting in an improved climate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4012</Index>
			<!-- "planet name has ..."-->
			<Text> has experienced a massive volcanic eruption \nThe environment has been severely damaged</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4013</Index>
			<Text>Load Modification</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4014</Index>
			<Text>Available Modifications</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4015</Index>
			<Text>Load Mods (Web)</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4016</Index>
			<Text>Clear Active</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4017</Index>
			<Text>Population Growth Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4018</Index>
			<Text>Production Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4019</Index>
			<Text>Research Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4020</Index>
			<Text>Diplomacy Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4021</Index>
			<Text>Troop Strength Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4022</Index>
			<Text>Ship Cost Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4023</Index>
			<Text>Ship Hitpoints Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4024</Index>
			<Text>Tax Income Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4025</Index>
			<Text>In-borders FTL Bonus</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4026</Index>
			<Text>FTL Speed Multiplier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4027</Index>
			<Text>FTL Power Drain Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4028</Index>
			<Text>Sublight Speed Bonus</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4029</Index>
			<Text>Sensor Range Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4030</Index>
			<Text>Spy Effectiveness Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4031</Index>
			<Text>Artifact Bonus Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4032</Index>
			<Text>Cannon Accuracy Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4033</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Damage/Radius Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4034</Index>
			<Text>Missile Hitpoints Bonus</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4035</Index>
			<Text>Missile Dodge Chance</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4036</Index>
			<Text>Ship Mass Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4037</Index>
			<Text>Maintenance Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4038</Index>
			<Text>In-system FTL speed</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4039</Index>
			<Text>Fuel Cell Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4040</Index>
			<Text>Minimum Population Growth</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4041</Index>
			<Text>Maximum Population Growth</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4042</Index>
			<Text>Unlocks a new Hull type: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4043</Index>
			<Text>Add ship designs to this fleet from the panel on the right. Use 'Shift' key to place multiple ships of the same type. When you are done, you can press the 'Requisition' button, which will search your empire for ships that can fill your fleet. If you do not have the ships, it will order that they are built at a suitable planet.\n\nReturn here at any time to requisition replacements for any ships that are lost in combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4044</Index>
			<Text>Modder Tools</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4045</Index>
			<Text>Tiny</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4046</Index>
			<Text>Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4046</Index>
			<Text>Normal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4047</Index>
			<Text>Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4048</Index>
			<Text>Epic</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4049</Index>
			<Text>Easy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4050</Index>
			<Text>Hard</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4051</Index>
			<Text>Brutal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4052</Index>
			<Text>Right Click to Expand</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4053</Index>
			<!-- as in "5 turns" remaining-->
			<Text>turns</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4054</Index>
			<Text>No Fleet Selected</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4055</Index>
			<Text>You are not currently editing a fleet. Click a hotkey on the left side of the screen to begin creating or editing the corresponding fleet.\n\nWhen you are finished editing, you can save your fleet design to disk for quick access in the future.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4056</Index>
			<Text>Fleet Design Overview</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4057</Index>
			<Text>Add ship designs to this fleet from the panel on the right. Use shift key to place multiple ships of the same type. When you are done, you can press the 'Requisition' button, which will search your empire for ships that can fill your fleet. If you do not have the ships, it will order that they are built at a suitable planet.\n\nReturn here at any time to requisition replacements for any ships that are lost in combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4056</Index>
			<Text>Fleet Design Overview</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4057</Index>
			<Text>Fighters Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4058</Index>
			<Text>Frigates Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4059</Index>
			<Text>Corvettes Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4060</Index>
			<Text>Cruisers Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4061</Index>
			<Text>Capitals Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4062</Index>
			<Text>Fleets Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4063</Index>
			<Text>Player Designs Only</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- governor types -->
		<Token>
			<Index>4064</Index>
			<Text>Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4065</Index>
			<Text>Industrial</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4066</Index>
			<Text>Agricultural</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4067</Index>
			<Text>Research</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4068</Index>
			<Text>Military</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4069</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Assets</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4070</Index>
			<Text>You may scrap this building by right clicking on it</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4071</Index>
			<Text>Increased Lifespans</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4072</Index>
			<Text>Spy Offense</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4073</Index>
			<Text>Spy Defense</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4074</Index>
			<Text>Phased Ordnance</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4075</Index>
			<Text>Super Soldiers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4076</Index>
			<Text>Resistance is Futile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4077</Index>
			<Text>Alien Language Studies</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4078</Index>
			<Text>Xeno-Linguistic Nuance</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4079</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Compilers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4080</Index>
			<Text>StarDrive Enhancement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4081</Index>
			<Text>Tachyons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4082</Index>
			<Text>Reaction Drive Upgrade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4083</Index>
			<Text>FTL Efficiency</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4084</Index>
			<Text>Slipstreams</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4085</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Effectiveness</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4086</Index>
			<Text>ECM Bonus</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4087</Index>
			<Text>Missile Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4088</Index>
			<Text>Top Guns</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4089</Index>
			<Text>Reactive Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4090</Index>
			<Text>Mass Reduction</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4091</Index>
			<Text>Hull Strengthening</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4092</Index>
			<Text>Armor Piercing</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4093</Index>
			<Text>Armor Phasing</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- even newer stuff-->
		<Token>
			<Index>4094</Index>
			<Text>Thought Crystal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4095</Index>
			<Text>This crystalline structure syncs with and amplifies the brain waves of biological organisms. Simply put, everything that gets near to it becomes smarter. +0.5 research per turn to the owner of this planet</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4096</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 research per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4097</Index>
			<Text>Commodities are special resources that are limited in number and provide unique bonuses to colonies that possess them. Commodities are harvested automatically at colonies where they occur naturally. They can then be moved throughout your empire using freighters. You may specify whether you wish to import or export any commodities you have access to in this panel.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4098</Index>
			<Text>Broadside Flak Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>4099</Index>
			<Text>This broadside-mounted cannon is capable of delivering a higher-powered kinetic blast than its turret-mounted cousins. Weapon mobility and target tracking are traded for the opportunity to unleash hellish volleys of unaimed fire.</Text>
		</Token>
	    <Token>
			<Index>5000</Index>
			<Text>For a ship to be warp capable, it must have a Warp Core installed. Warp Cores provide a Warpable Mass Capacity. If a ship's mass is less than or equal to a ship's Warpable Mass, then it can achieve faster than light travel.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5001</Index>
			<Text>Small Warp Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5002</Index>
			<Text>This warp core is small and inefficient but is capable of driving a ship farther and faster than any conventional propulsion system</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5003</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5004</Index>
			<Text>This fighter-bomber weapon has a relatively huge impact for its size. It has a small guidance package but relies on the momentum of its mothership for its speed. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5005</Index>
			<Text>Disruption Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5006</Index>
			<Text>An energy-based space bomb that is twice as effective versus shields </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5007</Index>
			<Text>Space Bombs</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5008</Index>
			<Text>With the proper equipment, swarms of small vessels can be a danger to even the largest ships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5009</Index>
			<Text>Warp Drive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5010</Index>
			<Text>Making an object with mass travel faster than the speed of light is not possible in real space. A warp drive achieves FTL travel by encasing a ship's mass in a subspace bubble, effectively removing it from real space while the drive is engaged. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5011</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Tunneling</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5012</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Tunneling is the science of identifying the most efficient route between two real space points in the decidedly more complicated web of subspace </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5013</Index>
			<Text>Core Integration</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5014</Index>
			<Text>By integrating new advances in the fields of cooling and power transfer, we are able to build a larger and more efficient warp core suited for use in capital ships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5015</Index>
			<Text>Maneuvering Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5016</Index>
			<Text>A balanced engine that provides decent thrusting and maneuvering capabilities as well as an afterburner for inter-system travel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5017</Index>
			<Text>Range Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5018</Index>
			<Text>This engine has only two states: off or full burn. It is not suitable as a maneuvering engine but is the most efficient engine for sublight inter-system travel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5019</Index>
			<Text>Combat Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5020</Index>
			<Text>This engine provides excellent combat maneuvering and thrusting but has no afterburner capabilities. It is less efficient than other engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5021</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Rocketry</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5022</Index>
			<Text>Advances in cooling and propellant delivery mechanisms are allowing us to reach farther and farther into the stars.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5023</Index>
			<Text>Sublight speeds are increased by 15%</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5024</Index>
			<Text>Nuclear Drive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5025</Index>
			<Text>While it may not seem entirely safe to do so, we have discovered that we can create small nuclear explosions behind our ships and capture this energy to reach interstellar targets</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5026</Index>
			<Text>Afterburner speeds are increased by 25%</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5027</Index>
			<Text>Impulse Drive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5028</Index>
			<Text>The theory for the Impulse Drive is similar to the Nuclear Drive. The real advancement is in our ability to control the strength of the explosions, allowing a more general application of the technology</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5029</Index>
			<Text>Sublight speeds are increased by 15%</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5030</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5031</Index>
			<Text>This newest generation of engines provides larger, more powerful, and more efficient sublight thrusters</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5032</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Combat Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5033</Index>
			<Text>A combat thruster featuring an improved thrust to power ratio</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5034</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Range Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5035</Index>
			<Text>A more powerful and efficient frigate-sized afterburner meant for long-range burns</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5036</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Maneuvering Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5037</Index>
			<Text>A balanced and efficient frigate engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5038</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5039</Index>
			<Text>Bigger, better, and more efficient than earlier designs, these engines are suitable for usage on cruiser class vessels</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5040</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Range Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5041</Index>
			<Text>A large and efficient cruiser-class afterburner engine for making long range sublight burns</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5042</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Maneuvering Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5043</Index>
			<Text>A balanced cruiser engine with good combat and afterburner performance</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5044</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Combat Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5045</Index>
			<Text>A high-powered engine designed to provide combat maneuverability to cruiser-class vessels</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5046</Index>
			<Text>Titan Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5047</Index>
			<Text>The pinnacle of sublight engine technology, these engines are meant for the largest of ships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5048</Index>
			<Text>Titan Combat Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5049</Index>
			<Text>A monstrous and powerful engine for sublight combat maneuvers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5051</Index>
			<Text>Titan Range Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5052</Index>
			<Text>A titanic afterburner for sublight acceleration</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5053</Index>
			<Text>Titan Maneuvering Thruster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5054</Index>
			<Text>A massive and balanced engine for use on the largest ships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5055</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Mount</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5056</Index>
			<Text>When our scientists thought about how to make Space Bombs more effective, the best they could come up with was to make a bigger bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5057</Index>
			<Text>MOASB</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5058</Index>
			<Text>This weapon is affectionately called the Mother of All Space Bombs due to its huge blast effect</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5059</Index>
			<Text>PD Focus</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5060</Index>
			<Text>The number of explosive threats in the galaxy mandates further investment in point defense weaponry</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5061</Index>
			<Text>Rapid Loading</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5062</Index>
			<Text>All point defense weapons receive a 25% bonus to their rate of fire</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5063</Index>
			<Text>All point defense weapons receive a 25% bonus to the speed of their projectiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5064</Index>
			<Text>All point defense weapons receive a 25% bonus to their range</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5065</Index>
			<Text>Capital Warp Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5066</Index>
			<Text>The beating heart of a capital ship, this warp core is massive, powerful, and efficient</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5067</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Containment</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5068</Index>
			<Text>Building large reactors that are fit for space travel is really a matter of containing the radioactive and thermal output of the reactor to protect ship crew and systems</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5069</Index>
			<Text>Reactor Fuel Cell</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5070</Index>
			<Text>This cell stores reactor fuel suitable for use in Warp Reactor and afterburner engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5071</Index>
			<Text>Power Capacitor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5072</Index>
			<Text>This device stores power, which is required for the operation of many ship systems including shields, weapons, and certain types of engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5073</Index>
			<Text>Fissionable Material</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5074</Index>
			<Text>These rare metals are raw materials suitable for refinement into usable reactor fuel. A fuel refinery is required to process these materials.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5075</Index>
			<Text>Fuel Refinery</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5076</Index>
			<Text>This building converts raw Fissionable Materials into usable Reactor Fuel, creating 100 reactor fuel per 1 Fissionable Material available each turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5077</Index>
			<Text>Converts Fissionables to Fuel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5078</Index>
			<Text>Fissionables Mine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5079</Index>
			<Text>A mine that extracts raw Fissionable Materials from a planet with the Fissionable Materials Resource. The more Fissionable Materials resources a planet has, the faster the extraction</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5080</Index>
			<Text>Extracts Raw Fissionables</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5081</Index>
			<Text>Industrialized Homeworld</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5082</Index>
			<Text>Trees? Who needs trees. What your people needed was room for more factories. +1 homeworld richness, -1 homeworld fertility</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5083</Index>
			<Text>Ascension</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5084</Index>
			<Text>The data-stream from the Remnant Mothership holds the key to the Mystery of the Remnant. We need to study it immediately, before we're all destroyed!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5085</Index>
			<Text>As the Remnant Exterminators sweep across the galaxy, burning and killing all that they find, you step inside the completed Ascension Array. In one glorious moment you are given True Knowledge. You are all things that have ever lived. You know all the joys and sorrows of your people and every people to ever populate the galaxy. You experience lives beyond counting. You are Father and Son reunited, friend and foe, predator and prey. You are the light at the end of the tunnel. \n \n And you are not alone.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5086</Index>
			<Text>WARNING: CPU INTENSE! This option will force a full combat simulation for 100% accuracy even when battles are occurring out of sight and between non-player factions. If this option is unchecked, an approximation will be used to speed up the game instead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5090</Index>
			<Text>Space Trash</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5091</Index>
			<Text>You are the worst race in the known universe. A worthless piece of trash that can't do anything right and deserves to be annihilated!</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Oasis-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5092</Index>
			<Text>Oasis</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5093</Index>
			<Text>A fresh water reservoir surrounded by fertile soil and lush plant life.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5094</Index>
			<Text>Produces +0.7 food per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Underground superstructure-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5095</Index>
			<Text>Underground superstructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5096</Index>
			<Text>A huge, cleverly hidden subterranean complex, evidently constructed for a large population to take shelter. With such advanced technology, what could these people have been afraid of?</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5097</Index>
			<Text>Provides shelter for a large amount of population.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Ancient megacity-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5098</Index>
			<Text>Ancient megacity</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5099</Index>
			<Text>An enormous pyramid-shaped structure, lined with advanced tunnels and rooms. These constructions are seen throughout the history of many ancient civilizations, all related to unsettlingly similar religious entities.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5100</Index>
			<Text>Provides housing for a large amount of population.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!--Drone platform-->
		<Token>
			<Index>5101</Index>
			<Text>Drone platform</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5102</Index>
			<Text>Self sustaining planetary defense. This platform automatically launches a swarm of drones to fight enemy ships near the planet. Requires Drone technology to operate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5103</Index>
			<Text>Planetary defense system. Attacks foes with a swarm of drones.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tim's -->
		<Token>
			<Index>5223</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5224</Index>
			<Text>Long Range Missiles are designed to out-range any other weapon. This comes with the drawback of slower missile speeds and maneuverability, but it contains multiple warhead system designed to decrease chances of interception.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5225</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5226</Index>
			<Text>The mark II has a decent range and damage improvement over the mark I.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5227</Index>
			<Text>LRM Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5228</Index>
			<Text>The mark III has a substantial range and damage improvement over the mark II.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5229</Index>
			<Text>Gauss Sniper Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5230</Index>
			<Text>A high speed Gauss rifle with great range and damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5231</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Repeater Auto Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5232</Index>
			<Text>This heavy auto cannon fires a massive spread of bullets, at a decent range</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5233</Index>
			<Text>PD Green Laser Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5234</Index>
			<Text>This variant fires slower and in small bursts</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5235</Index>
			<Text>PD Purple Laser Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5236</Index>
			<Text>This variant fires very fast</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5237</Index>
			<Text>Large Fabricator and Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5238</Index>
			<Text>This Facility is a large ordnance storage which has a dedicated fabricator module. It is very power hungry.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5239</Index>
			<Text>Armored Ordnance Locker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5240</Index>
			<Text>Small armored ordnance lockers provide storage and defense</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5241</Index>
			<Text>Sustained Support</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5242</Index>
			<Text>Self sufficiency is extremely important in long and drawn out combat situations. Our engineers came up with this solution, a large fabricator and storage bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5243</Index>
			<Text>Second Warehouse</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5244</Index>
			<Text>A second warehouse provides storage for 150 extra food and production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5245</Index>
			<Text>+150 maximum goods storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5246</Index>
			<Text>Third Warehouse</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5247</Index>
			<Text>A third warehouse provides storage for 150 extra food and production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5248</Index>
			<Text>+150 maximum goods storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5249</Index>
			<Text>X-Ray Pulse Beam</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5250</Index>
			<Text>X-Ray Pulse Beam turret fires rays of deadly X-Ray lasers in quick succession. It has near perfect accuracy and short to medium range, which makes it a good anti-fighter weapon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5251</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Anti-Matter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5252</Index>
			<Text>Fires a fast burst of supercharged Anti-Matter shells over great distances. Does extra damage to Shields and Armor and has a 60% chance to bypass Shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5253</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Weapons I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5254</Index>
			<Text>By further stabilizing matter / anti-matter reactions, we have managed to weaponize our research into powerful anti-matter weaponry.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5255</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Anti-Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5256</Index>
			<Text>This is a fighter specific small version of the Anti-Matter Reactor. It has very good power output, but it explodes if destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5257</Index>
			<Text>Large Adamantite Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5258</Index>
			<Text>An incredibly strong neutronium laced alloy resistant to all forms of damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5259</Index>
			<Text>Medium Adamantite Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5260</Index>
			<Text>An incredibly strong neutronium laced alloy resistant to all forms of damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5261</Index>
			<Text>Small Adamantite Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5262</Index>
			<Text>An incredibly strong neutronium laced alloy resistant to all forms of damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5263</Index>
			<Text>Large Tritanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5264</Index>
			<Text>An extremely high strength and temperature resistant alloy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5265</Index>
			<Text>Medium Tritanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5266</Index>
			<Text>An extremely high strength and temperature resistant alloy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5267</Index>
			<Text>Small Tritanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5268</Index>
			<Text>An extremely high strength and temperature resistant alloy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5269</Index>
			<Text>Adamantite Alloys</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5270</Index>
			<Text>An incredibly strong neutronium laced alloy resistant to all forms of damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5271</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Alloys</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5272</Index>
			<Text>An extremely high strength and temperature resistant alloy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5273</Index>
			<Text>Asteroid Base</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5274</Index>
			<Text>Build your very own asteroid base in a safe orbit around your home planet. Featuring every modern commodity to which you have become accustomed. Exactly the thing that every humanoid species needs!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5275</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Velocity Vulcan Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5276</Index>
			<Text>HV Vulcan cannons fire at velocities so high that the strength of materials upon impact is very small compared to inertial stresses. Thus, even metals behave like fluids under hyper-velocity impact. Extreme hyper-velocity results in vaporization of the impactor and target. They are very effective versus armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5277</Index>
			<Text>Small Regenerating Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5278</Index>
			<Text>This armor can withstand a decent amount of damage. Where it shines however is with the nano repair bots that are released when the ship starts taking damage, healing every module on the ship. The effects of the equipped armor modules are cumulative and a ship equipped with regenerating armor is a force to be reckoned with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5279</Index>
			<Text>Regenerating Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5280</Index>
			<Text>This armor can withstand a decent amount of damage. Where it shines however is with the nano repair bots that are released when the ship starts taking damage, healing every module on the ship. The effects of the equipped armor modules are cumulative and a ship equipped with regenerating armor is a force to be reckoned with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5281</Index>
			<Text>Shielded Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5282</Index>
			<Text>Recent advances in miniaturization, shielding and energy research have allowed us to incorporate a small electro-magnetic shield into our armor plating.
</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5283</Index>
			<Text>Small Shielded Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5284</Index>
			<Text>Recent advances in miniaturization, shielding and energy research have allowed us to incorporate a small electro-magnetic shield into our armor plating. Requires a power source to operate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5285</Index>
			<Text>Advanced LRM Platforms</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5286</Index>
			<Text>Better thrusters, faster missile engines, better targeting sensors, and increased payloads allow us to develop new LRM platforms.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5287</Index>
			<Text>Advanced MRM Systems</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5288</Index>
			<Text>We can focus our efforts on improving our medium range missiles arsenal. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5289</Index>
			<Text>Improved LRM Platforms</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5290</Index>
			<Text>Better thrusters and improved targeting sensors allow us to develop new LRM systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5291</Index>
			<Text>Shadow Storm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5292</Index>
			<Text>A rapid fire, short range burst missile platform. Especially deadly against smaller fast moving ships, it functions most practically as an anti fighter/corvette weapon. It features a wide targeting angle, and a slight chance to penetrate enemy shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5293</Index>
			<Text>Shadow Storm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5294</Index>
			<Text>Prototype SRM platform. A rapid fire, short range burst missile platform. Especially deadly versus smaller and fast moving ships, this was designed mainly as an anti fighter/corvette weapon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5295</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5296</Index>
			<Text>A plasma projector uses a massive array of plasma generating nodes to project a storm of high-energy plasma shells towards a target.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5297</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Plasma Weapons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5298</Index>
			<Text>We are now able to build heavier plasma weapons by using the previous ionized reactor Plasma and pushing it to new limits with higher pressure. The magnetized pressure system requires, however, more constant power and even extra reactor power to fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5299</Index>
			<Text>Upgrades</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5300</Index>
			<Text>Various research options to upgrade ship and weapon components and more.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5301</Index>
			<Text>Plasteel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5302</Index>
			<Text>Although steel armor is inexpensive, it is extremely heavy and reduces the maneuverability of our ships significantly. By focusing our research efforts into developing new construction materials, we have discovered a new alloy. It is slightly weaker than steel, but very easy to repair.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5303</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5304</Index>
			<Text>An anti-matter projector uses a massive array of anti-matter generating nodes to project a storm of highly unstable anti-matter shells towards a target. It has a 25% chance to bypass Shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5305</Index>
			<Text>Menoetius Launch Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5306</Index>
			<Text>The Menoetius launch bay launches 4 mines. They have a 33% chance to penetrate even the strongest shields. Once they get through the shield their internal reactors will cause a violent chain reaction making them explode with tremendous force. Vulnerable to PD weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5307</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5308</Index>
			<Text>A sphere of anti-matter contained in a magnetic field that releases upon impact, allowing the anti-matter to explode. Can be shot down. It has a 50% chance to bypass Shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5309</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5310</Index>
			<Text>A sphere of plasma contained in a magnetic field that releases upon impact, allowing the plasma sphere to explode. Can be shot down.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5311</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Weapons II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5312</Index>
			<Text>Our scientists have made a breakthrough in their research towards matter / anti-matter reactions, granting us access to a new weapon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5313</Index>
			<Text>Emp Mine Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5314</Index>
			<Text>Emp mines attempt to strike vulnerable systems and sensors in an effort to temporarily stop ships from attacking. Vulnerable to PD weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5315</Index>
			<Text>Rapid Fire Lasers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5316</Index>
			<Text>Rapid Fire Lasers, or Blue lasers, are fast firing laser cannons specially designed for fighters and corvettes. Blue colored projectiles fire in rapid succession, causing the weapon to go into a long cooling period. Ideal weapon for fast moving ships using strafing runs. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5317</Index>
			<Text>Shield Buster Mine Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5318</Index>
			<Text>Shield buster mines specialize in quickly depleting the shields of enemy ships. Vulnerable to PD weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5319</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Armor Mine Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5320</Index>
			<Text>Anti-armor mines are armed with special high explosive charges to penetrate even the thickest hulls. Vulnerable to PD weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5321</Index>
			<Text>Small Mine Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5322</Index>
			<Text>The small mine launcher casts out a single explosive mine. Lacks the operating range of the larger versions but can easily be mounted on smaller hulls. Vulnerable to PD weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5327</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Repeater Auto Cannon AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5328</Index>
			<Text>This heavy auto cannon is equipped with armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5329</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Repeater Auto Cannon HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5330</Index>
			<Text>This heavy auto cannon is equipped with high explosive armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5331</Index>
			<Text>Light Repeater Auto Cannon AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5332</Index>
			<Text>This light auto cannon is equipped with armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5333</Index>
			<Text>Light Repeater Auto Cannon HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5334</Index>
			<Text>This light auto cannon is equipped with high explosive armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5335</Index>
			<Text>Light Repeater Auto Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5336</Index>
			<Text>The light auto cannon fires a steady stream of bullets providing a barrage of suppressive fire where needed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5323</Index>
			<Text>Scythe Machine Gun H</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5324</Index>
			<Text>The Scythe machine gun is an excellent deterrent to small fighters and tracking weapons. It fires a near constant stream of bullets at anything that dares to get near.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5325</Index>
			<Text>Scythe Machine Gun V</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5326</Index>
			<Text>The Scythe machine gun is an excellent deterrent to small fighters and tracking weapons. It fires a near constant stream of bullets at anything that dares to get near.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5337</Index>
			<Text>LRM Single Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5338</Index>
			<Text>A single LRM missile launcher, convenient and deadly.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5339</Index>
			<Text>MRM Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5340</Index>
			<Text>This MRM platform launches a salvo of 8 missiles at unsuspecting targets. This weapon can easily overwhelm even the most potent point defense systems with its Terminal Phase system.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5341</Index>
			<Text>Railgun Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5342</Index>
			<Text>Two railguns mounted on a swivel turret. A very efficient weapon system.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5343</Index>
			<Text>Gauss Sniper Cannon AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5344</Index>
			<Text>A high speed Gauss rifle with great range and damage, armed with armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5345</Index>
			<Text>Gauss Sniper Cannon HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5346</Index>
			<Text>A high speed Gauss rifle with great range and damage, armed with high explosive armor piercing rounds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5347</Index>
			<Text>Guided Weapons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5348</Index>
			<Text>Research and discover a wide array of guided, self propelled weapon systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5349</Index>
			<Text>Anti-fighter Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5350</Index>
			<Text>This set of technologies will improve our ability to effectively combat the many smaller ships on a battlefield. In addition to anti-fighter missiles which can be equiped on our own fighters, we can also manufacture Storm weapons for our larger vessels, swivel turrets that are excellent at targeting small enemy ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5351</Index>
			<Text>Sniper Systems</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5352</Index>
			<Text>The Gauss Cannon is a type of projectile accelerator consisting of one or more coils used as electromagnets in the configuration of a linear motor that accelerate a ferromagnetic or conducting projectile to high velocity. We can create cannons which use electro magnet accelerators to fire very accurate and very high speed projectiles. Hence the name - "Sniper"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5353</Index>
			<Text>Sniper Systems AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5354</Index>
			<Text>We can now modify our Gauss Cannon projectile to use armor piercing components while maintaining almost the same accuracy and speed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5355</Index>
			<Text>Sniper Systems HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5356</Index>
			<Text>The addition of High Explosives to our sniper cannons could make them even more useful.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5357</Index>
			<Text>Suppressive Fire</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5358</Index>
			<Text>Rapid fire autocannons fill the skies with lead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5359</Index>
			<Text>Suppressive Fire AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5360</Index>
			<Text>Rapid fire autocannons fill the skies with lead. These variants are equipped with armor piercing ammunition.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5361</Index>
			<Text>Suppressive Fire HEAP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5362</Index>
			<Text>Rapid fire autocannons fill the skies with lead. These variants are equipped with high explosive armor piercing ammunition.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5365</Index>
			<Text>Ancient Pillar</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5366</Index>
			<Text>This ancient pillar appears to be highly valuable. Our scientists are eager to find out what they do. They suggest you send some troops to investigate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5367</Index>
			<Text>Large Warehouse</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5368</Index>
			<Text>At one time an abandoned warehouse, now cleaned and fixed up, this large warehouse provides storage for 200 extra food and production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5369</Index>
			<Text>+200 maximum goods storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5373</Index>
			<Text>Manufacturing Plant Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5374</Index>
			<Text>Use this module in combination with the normal colonization module. This module contains a small manufacturing plant, providing a +0.5 bonus to production on the newly colonized planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5375</Index>
			<Text>Food Replicator Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5376</Index>
			<Text>Use this module in combination with the normal colonization module. This module contains a small food replicator, providing a +0.5 bonus to food on the newly colonized planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5377</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Grav Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5378</Index>
			<Text>This heavy cannon fires a lethal volley of Graviton particles, compressed in a high density tritanium coating. Upon impact, this coating ruptures, releasing an extremely violent tide of gravitational forces. Shields will lessen its destructive power, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5379</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Grav Rounds</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5380</Index>
			<Text>Weapons equipped with grav-rounds use anti-grav generators mounted inside large cannons. They do little impact damage, but create an aimed kinetic push effect, pushing any vessels away that are fired on.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5381</Index>
			<Text>Specialist Weapons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5382</Index>
			<Text>Weapons that do not fall into a specific category and are considered not part of the norm.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5383</Index>
			<Text>Research Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5384</Index>
			<Text>Use this module in combination with the normal colonization module. This module contains a small laboratory, providing a +0.25 bonus to research on the newly colonized planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5385</Index>
			<Text>Small Laboratory</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5386</Index>
			<Text>The small laboratory allows your scientists to get started with research efforts, mainly on new colonies with harsh environments. It is usually deployed by a Colony Ship and its biggest advantage is that it can be built even on uninhabitable tiles. But costs are high when built out of scope of a Colony Ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5387</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 research per turn, +40 Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5388</Index>
			<Text>Manufacturing Plant</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5389</Index>
			<Text>The manufacturing plant makes all kinds of useful items for early colony development and is usually deployed by a colony ship. Its biggest advantage is that it can be built even on uninhabitable tiles. But costs are high if built out of scope of a colony ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5390</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 flat production, +30 Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5391</Index>
			<Text>Food Replicator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5392</Index>
			<Text>The food replicator provides healthy, replicated food for a colony. Replication amounts are rather low, but it can be enough for an early stage colony, and might be sufficient for small mining colonies as well. Its biggest advantage is that it can be built even on uninhabitable tiles. But costs are high if built out of scope of a colony ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5393</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 food per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5394</Index>
			<Text>Military Outpost Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5395</Index>
			<Text>Use this module in combination with the normal colonization module. This module will deploy a Military Outpost to defend your colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5396</Index>
			<Text>Missile Silo Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5397</Index>
			<Text>Use this module in combination with the normal colonization module. This module will deploy a missile silo for long range colony defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5398</Index>
			<Text>Casino Underhive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5399</Index>
			<Text>Smugglers Underhive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5400</Index>
			<Text>Pit Slaves Underhive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5401</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Defense III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5402</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Defense II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5403</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Sniper Cannon Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5404</Index>
			<Text>Great range and pinpoint accuracy are what make this planetary weapon emplacement stand out.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5405</Index>
			<Text>Planetary AutoCannon Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5406</Index>
			<Text>Heavy and rapid suppressive fire should deter any unwelcome vessels from landing on our planets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5407</Index>
			<Text>Revoran Capital City</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5408</Index>
			<Text>Cloud Peak Missile Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5409</Index>
			<Text>Cloud Peak surface to space guided missiles have extreme range and are capable of providing defensive control over most of an entire star system.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5410</Index>
			<Text>Missile Defense I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5411</Index>
			<Text>Missile Defense II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5412</Index>
			<Text>It is wise to improve our planetary defense abilities with weapons that can deter invaders. A series of giant SAM launchers should be a good start.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5418</Index>
			<Text>Dragons Breath Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5419</Index>
			<Text>The Dragons Breath shotgun is a close combat weapon. The burning plasma rounds fired by this shotgun are designed to superheat the exposed areas it hits, melting away any defenses the ships might have.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5420</Index>
			<Text>Explosive Shells Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5421</Index>
			<Text>The E.S. shotgun is a close combat weapon. It is equipped with high explosive shells, dealing damage in a large area.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5422</Index>
			<Text>High Velocity Energizer Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5423</Index>
			<Text>The H.V.E shotgun is a close combat weapon. It is equipped with high velocity emp shells, capable of immobilizing enemy ships for short periods of time.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5424</Index>
			<Text>Repeater Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5425</Index>
			<Text>The Repeater shotgun is a close combat weapon, and a close cousin to the Flechette shotgun. It fires non-stop until it either runs out of ammo or destroys its target.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5426</Index>
			<Text>Shotguns are close combat weapons. They are designed to do heavy damage spread over an area. Depending on the type of ammo used, they can do different types of damage. These weapons fire fast and are accurate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5427</Index>
			<Text>Shotguns</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5428</Index>
			<Text>Shotgun Emp Rounds</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5429</Index>
			<Text>Shotgun Repeater</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5430</Index>
			<Text>Shotgun Explosives</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5431</Index>
			<Text>Shotgun Plasma</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5432</Index>
			<Text>Medium Regenerating Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5433</Index>
			<Text>This armor can withstand a decent amount of damage. Where it shines however is with the nano repair bots that are released when the ship starts taking damage, healing every module on the ship. The effects of the equipped armor modules are cumulative, and a ship equipped with regenerating armor is a force to be reckoned with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5434</Index>
			<Text>Large Regenerating Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5435</Index>
			<Text>This armor can withstand a decent amount of damage. Where it shines however is with the nano repair bots that are released when the ship starts taking damage, healing every module on the ship. The effects of the equipped armor modules are cumulative, and a ship equipped with regenerating armor is a force to be reckoned with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5436</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5437</Index>
			<Text>This plasma cannon is best mounted on frigates. It fires a stream of plasma shells towards unsuspecting targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5438</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5439</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Heavy Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5440</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Titan Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5441</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Emp Blaster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5442</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Blaster</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5443</Index>
			<Text>Forward Thruster 1x1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5444</Index>
			<Text>This is a small forward thruster, installed on the exterior of the ship and not on the usual dedicated engine space. Cost effective when more speed is needed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5445</Index>
			<Text>Forward Thruster 1x2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5446</Index>
			<Text>This is a slightly bigger forward thruster, installed on the exterior of the ship and not on the usual dedicated engine space. Cost effective when more speed is needed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5447</Index>
			<Text>Forward Thruster 1x3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5448</Index>
			<Text>This is big Anti-Matter forward thruster, installed on the exterior of the ship and not on the usual dedicated engine space. Cost effective when more speed is needed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5449</Index>
			<Text>Forward Thruster 1x4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5450</Index>
			<Text>This is very big Anti-Matter forward thruster, installed on the exterior of the ship and not on the usual dedicated engine space. Cost effective when more speed is needed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5451</Index>
			<Text>Warp Drive Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5452</Index>
			<Text>This is a dedicated Anit-Matter warp engine. Most of it can be installed inside the ship for greater protection. It does not provide Thrust or Turn Thrust.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5453</Index>
			<Text>Warp Drive Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5454</Index>
			<Text>This is a dedicated warp engine. Most of it can be installed inside the ship for greater protection. It does not provide Thrust or Turn Thrust. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5455</Index>
			<Text>Warp Drive Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5456</Index>
			<Text>This is a dedicated warp engine. Most of it can be installed inside the ship for greater protection. It does not provide Thrust or Turn Thrust. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5457</Index>
			<Text>Velocity Stimulance I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5458</Index>
			<Text>Velocity Stimulance II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5459</Index>
			<Text>Velocity Stimulance III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5460</Index>
			<Text>Velocity Stimulance IV</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5461</Index>
			<Text>Velocity Stimulance V</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5462</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. 
We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for fighter/corvettes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5463</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Green Laser</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5464</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Tech</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5465</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Planet Nuker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5466</Index>
			<Text>Experimental Gate Facility</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5467</Index>
			<Text>The Experimental Gate Facility comes with an active prototype stargate that can send your troops on away missions. Exploring new worlds and civilizations might bring with it new technologies, riches beyond your imagination or incredibly dangerous and potentially deadly encounters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5468</Index>
			<Text>Can open a two-way gate to far away worlds and galaxies.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5469</Index>
			<Text>Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5470</Index>
			<Text>The Magnetic Accelerator Cannon is an immensely powerful weapon, capable of destroying small vessels in one shot, whether they have shields or not. Because it is so large, heavy, and power hungry, only Titan class ships should use these.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5471</Index>
			<Text>A medium cargo hold with rudimentary life support capabilities. This particular hold can store 9 units of either food or production, or a small number of colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5472</Index>
			<Text>Medium Cargo Hold</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5473</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Magnetic Accelerator Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5474</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Regen Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5475</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Magnetic Accelerator Cannon 2x2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5476</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Combat Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5477</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Plasma Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5478</Index>
			<Text>Blue Laser Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5479</Index>
			<Text>The first generation of Rapid Fire Lasers designed for fighters. This is mainly a first working prototype for this type of energy weapon. Its main con is a long delay between bursts, necessary for the weapon to cool.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5480</Index>
			<Text>Blue Laser Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5481</Index>
			<Text>Improved Version of Mk1. Thanks to the larger size of heat sinks, it can maintain rapid fire for longer periods of time, increasing the number of projectiles fired. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5482</Index>
			<Text>Blue Laser Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5483</Index>
			<Text>An advanced rapid fire Laser that can fit in a fighter hull. Thanks to the bigger advanced rail type magnetic barrel, projectiles can be fired from a larger distance, and each shot has increased energy storage for more devastation on impact</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5484</Index>
			<Text>Green Heavy Laser Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5485</Index>
			<Text>Green version of the standard heavy laser cannon. It has been modified to have higher damage per shot and greater range, but also lower fire rate. It is also slightly better versus Shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5486</Index>
			<Text>Purple Heavy Laser Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5487</Index>
			<Text>Purple version of the standard heavy laser cannon. It has been modified to have lower damage per shot, but faster fire rate. It has a very small chance to completely bypass shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5488</Index>
			<Text>Medium Range Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5489</Index>
			<Text>Multi purpose missiles are a military standard in space combat, they were created for trading fire with any ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5490</Index>
			<Text>Long Range Support Missile.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>5491</Index>
			<Text>Long Range Support Missile turrets were created for vessels that can't go toe to toe with enemy heavy hitters. Ideal for Carriers so they can stay out of enemy range and contirbute to the battle.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- all new armor med and large description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>5999</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the small module. It is also more efficient and usually more cost effective than multiple smaller modules stacked to the same size. See the Small module description for armor details.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- SD Code Mod, UI ELEMENT TEXT -->
		<Token>
			<Index>6000</Index>
			<Text>sensor range</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6001</Index>
			<Text>subspace projection area</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6002</Index>
			<Text>Gravity Well Radius</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6003</Index>
			<Text>Defines the radius of planetary gravity wells. Larger values means ships need to be further away from a planetary body to engage FTL, et vice versa.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6004</Index>
			<Text>ECM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6005</Index>
			<Text>ECM Resist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6006</Index>
			<Text>Beam Dur</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6007</Index>
			<Text>Pause On Notifications</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6008</Index>
			<Text>Boarding</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6009</Index>
			<Text>Station</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6010</Index>
			<Text>Corvette</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6011</Index>
			<Text>Power Warp</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6012</Index>
			<Text>Repair Rate Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6013</Index>
			<Text>Repair Rate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6014</Index>
			<Text>Reactor Power Modifier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6015</Index>
			<Text>Hull Bonus: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6016</Index>
			<Text>Armor Protection</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6017</Index>
			<Text>Sensor Range</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6018</Index>
			<Text>Max Speed</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6019</Index>
			<Text>Cargo Space</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6020</Index>
			<Text>Fire Rate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6021</Index>
			<Text>Cost Reduction</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6022</Index>
			<Text>Prevent AI Federations</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6023</Index>
			<Text>Level</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6024</Index>
			<Text>Recovering</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6025</Index>
			<Text>has successfully complete training\nThe Agent's performance exceeded expectation.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6026</Index>
			<Text>has successfully completed training\nand has gained valuable knowledge.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6027</Index>
			<Text>was injured in a training accident.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6028</Index>
			<Text>was killed in a training accident.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6029</Index>
			<Text>has completed training, but failed to learn anything useful.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6030</Index>
			<Text>successfully infiltrated a colony:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6031</Index>
			<Text>\nThe Agent was not detected.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6032</Index>
			<Text>was unable to infiltrate a colony\nand was wounded avoiding capture</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6033</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent was foiled trying to infiltrate a colony\nThe Agent was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6034</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to infiltrate a colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6035</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent was killed trying to infiltrate one of our colonies\nThe Agent was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6036</Index>
			<Text>was unable to infiltrate a colony\nand had to abort the mission to avoid capture</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6037</Index>
			<Text>One of our Agents was assassinated:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6038</Index>
			<Text>could not assassinate an enemy Agent \nbecause target empire has no Agents</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6039</Index>
			<Text>assassinated an enemy Agent:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6040</Index>
			<Text>\nOur agent escaped unharmed and undetected.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6041</Index>
			<Text>\nThe Assassin was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6042</Index>
			<Text>\nOur agent was detected but escaped.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6043</Index>
			<Text>We managed to detect an enemy Assassin before it could strike\nThe Assassin was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6044</Index>
			<Text>was wounded trying to assassinate an enemy agent, but managed to escape.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6045</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent was killed during an assassination attempt\nThe Assassin was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6046</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to assassinate an enemy agent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6047</Index>
			<Text>was foiled trying to assassinate an enemy agent, but managed to escape.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6048</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent has sabotaged production on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6049</Index>
			<Text>\nThe Agent was sent by</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6050</Index>
			<Text>was detected while attempting to steal a technology\nand was wounded while escaping</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6051</Index>
			<Text>We foiled an enemy Agent trying to sabotage production on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6052</Index>
			<Text>was wounded while trying to sabotage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6053</Index>
			<Text>We killed an enemy Agent trying to sabotage production on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6054</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to sabotage an enemy colony</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6055</Index>
			<Text>escaped after being detected while trying to sabotage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6056</Index>
			<Text>An enemy spy stole some technology from us \nbut we don't know who they were working for</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6057</Index>
			<Text>stole a technology:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6058</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent stole a technology from us:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6059</Index>
			<Text>We foiled an enemy plot to steal our technology</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6060</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent was killed trying to steal our technology</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6061</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to steal technology</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6062</Index>
			<Text>was detected while attempting to steal a technology\nbut managed to escape unharmed</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6063</Index>
			<Text>aborted the Steal Technology mission because\nthere is nothing to steal;</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6064</Index>
			<Text>Credits are therefore refunded.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6065</Index>
			<Text>credits were mysteriously stolen from our treasury.\nWe have no suspects in the theft</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6066</Index>
			<Text>could not rob</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6067</Index>
			<Text>\nbecause they have no money</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6068</Index>
			<Text>stole</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6069</Index>
			<Text>credits from</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6070</Index>
			<Text>credits were stolen from our treasury by an enemy Agent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6071</Index>
			<Text>We foiled an enemy plot to rob our treasury</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6072</Index>
			<Text>was unable to steal any credits\nand was wounded while escaping.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6073</Index>
			<Text>We killed an enemy Agent during an attempted robbery</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6074</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to steal credits from</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6075</Index>
			<Text>was unable to steal any credits\nbut managed to escape unharmed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6076</Index>
			<Text>We foiled an enemy plot to incite rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6077</Index>
			<Text>incited a serious rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6078</Index>
			<Text>An enemy Agent has incited rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6079</Index>
			<Text>\nHowever, they know we are behind it.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6080</Index>
			<Text>was wounded while trying to incite a rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6081</Index>
			<Text>We killed an enemy agent trying to incite rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6082</Index>
			<Text>was killed trying to incite rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6083</Index>
			<Text>escaped after being detected while trying to incite rebellion on</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6084</Index>
			<Text>sabotaged production for</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6085</Index>
			<Text>turns:</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6086</Index>
			<Text>has recovered from their injuries.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6087</Index>
			<Text>has been promoted, and gains +1 Level.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6088</Index>
			<Text>Espionage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6089</Index>
			<Text>Espionage Overview</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6090</Index>
			<Text>Espionage Agents</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6091</Index>
			<Text>Intelligence Report</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6092</Index>
			<Text>Agent Dossier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6093</Index>
			<Text>Capital Elimination</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6094</Index>
			<Text>Home World: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6095</Index>
			<Text>Total Planets: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6096</Index>
			<Text>Total Starships: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6097</Index>
			<Text>Treasury: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6098</Index>
			<Text>Maintenance Costs: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6099</Index>
			<Text>Total Spies: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6100</Index>
			<Text>Population: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6101</Index>
			<Text>billion</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6102</Index>
			<Text>: Government Destroyed</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6103</Index>
			<Text> and Trade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6104</Index>
			<Text>: Trade Partner</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6105</Index>
			<Text>: No Diplomatic Relations</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6106</Index>
			<Text>Controls Home World: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6107</Index>
			<Text>Yes</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6108</Index>
			<Text>Alias: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6109</Index>
			<Text>Home: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6110</Index>
			<Text>Age: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6111</Index>
			<Text>Service: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6112</Index>
			<Text>Training Exercises: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6113</Index>
			<Text>Agents Assassinated: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6114</Index>
			<Text>Colonies Infiltrated: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6115</Index>
			<Text>Colonies Sabotaged: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6116</Index>
			<Text>Technologies Stolen: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6117</Index>
			<Text>Treasuries Robbed: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6118</Index>
			<Text>Rebellions Started: </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6119</Index>
			<Text> years</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6120</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance/s</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6121</Index>
			<Text>Range+</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6122</Index>
			<Text>Delay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6123</Index>
			<Text>Trans Pw</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6124</Index>
			<Text>Trans Ord</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6125</Index>
			<Text>Gross Income</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6126</Index>
			<Text>Expenditure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6127</Index>
			<Text>Net Income</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6128</Index>
			<Text>Land</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6129</Index>
			<Text>Net Losses</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6130</Index>
			<Text>Sensor Range</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6131</Index>
			<Text>Heal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6132</Index>
			<Text>Troop Capacity</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6133</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Added</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6134</Index>
			<Text>Prototype</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- XX01 -->
		<Token>
			<Index>6501</Index>
			<Text>missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6502</Index>
			<Text>missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6503</Index>
			<Text>Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6504</Index>
			<Text>Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6505</Index>
			<Text>Dual Guided Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6506</Index>
			<Text>Dual Guided Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6507</Index>
			<Text>Defense</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6508</Index>
			<Text>This research branch will focus on the means of defending our ships and colonies from enemy fire. We have several fields we can begin research in. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6509</Index>
			<Text>Electronics and Shield defence</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6510</Index>
			<Text>Electronics and Shield defence</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6511</Index>
			<Text>Reactors and Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6512</Index>
			<Text>Reactors and Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6513</Index>
			<Text>Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6514</Index>
			<Text>Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6515</Index>
			<Text>ArmoredTorpedoBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6516</Index>
			<Text>ArmoredTorpedoBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6517</Index>
			<Text>ArmoredTorpedoBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6518</Index>
			<Text>Heavily armored torpedo tube launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6519</Index>
			<Text>Tactical Nuke</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6520</Index>
			<Text>A tactical nuclear weapon, or non-strategic nuclear weapon, is a nuclear weapon which is designed to be used on a battlefield in military situations, mostly with friendly forces in proximity. Adapted for space usage, nuclear effects are less profound than with atmospheric detonations, but still often cause EMP damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6521</Index>
			<Text>Tactical nuke</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6522</Index>
			<Text>Nuclear tactical missile. Can cause devastating effects and also EMP damage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6523</Index>
			<Text>ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6524</Index>
			<Text>ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6525</Index>
			<Text>ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6526</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Ship missiles, much more powerful than regular missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6527</Index>
			<Text>Dual ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6528</Index>
			<Text>Dual Anti Capital Ship missiles. We also improved the ATCM itself, introducing slightly increased range and damage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6529</Index>
			<Text>Dual ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6530</Index>
			<Text>Dual Anti Capital Ship missiles. We also improved the ATCM itself, introducing slightly increased range and damage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6531</Index>
			<Text>AMX50 Revolver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6532</Index>
			<Text>An experimental Oscillating mounted missile launcher. Very expensive, but can launch 6 improved versions of ATCSM at a time.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6533</Index>
			<Text>AMX50 Revolver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6534</Index>
			<Text>An experimental Oscillating mounted missile launcher. Very expensive, but can launch 6 improved versions of ATCSM at a time. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6535</Index>
			<Text>XTL7 Werewolf</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6536</Index>
			<Text>An experimental weapon designed for the next generation of Torpedo Launchers. Well armored, but costly.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6537</Index>
			<Text>XTL7 Werewolf</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6538</Index>
			<Text>An experimental weapon designed for the next generation of Torpedo Launchers. Well armored, but costly.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6539</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Missile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6540</Index>
			<Text>smaller version of heavy missile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6541</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Missile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6542</Index>
			<Text>smaller version of heavy missile.Ammo:10</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6543</Index>
			<Text>Fighter ATCSM</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6544</Index>
			<Text>This is a Fighter version of the ATCSM. Smaller size, but decreased range and damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6545</Index>
			<Text>AssaultRaiders</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6546</Index>
			<Text>Bigger always means better!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6547</Index>
			<Text>StarLancers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6548</Index>
			<Text>These hangars are able to store even bigger ships than any other previous hangars, biggest benefit from StarLancers is their ability to relaunch ships way faster after they get destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6549</Index>
			<Text>Repair Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6550</Index>
			<Text>Mounted on large ships, this Repair Bay will significantly add to the the ship's repair capacity. It also contains a small power plant, making it useful as an auxiliary power conductor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6551</Index>
			<Text>InternalFighterBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6552</Index>
			<Text>Internal FighterBay, can install inside the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6553</Index>
			<Text>Internal BattleRaiders</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6554</Index>
			<Text>Internal BattleRaider bay, can install inside the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6555</Index>
			<Text>Internal AssaultBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6556</Index>
			<Text>Internal AssaultRaider bay, can install inside the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6557</Index>
			<Text>Internal LancerBay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6558</Index>
			<Text>Internal StarLancer bay, can install inside the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6559</Index>
			<Text>Electro Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6560</Index>
			<Text>This is a combination of early stage Metal armor, with the addition of solar collectors. These collectors, though providing less power flow than simple and armored solar panels, do also store a small amount of power within. Drawbacks are higher cost, and lower rigidity (even lower than Internal Bulkheads). As a bonus, they have some resistance to beam weapons, since the collectors need heat in order to provide power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6561</Index>
			<Text>Reactive Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6562</Index>
			<Text>This is the first improvement over steel armor. Reactive armor reacts in a certain way with offensive ordnance. It is stronger than Steel Armor, but costs more. It performs a little better against kinetic weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6563</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6564</Index>
			<Text>This Armor is slightly stronger than Reactive Armor, weighing less but costing more. It's Kinetics Resistance is improved and it has some Beam Resistance. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6565</Index>
			<Text>Reactive Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6566</Index>
			<Text>Stronger than steel and has some resistance to Kinetics</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6567</Index>
			<Text>Reactive Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6568</Index>
			<Text>Reactive Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6569</Index>
			<Text>Composite Alloys</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6570</Index>
			<Text>Twice as strong as Steel Armor, a little bit lighter, and 4 times the cost. This armor provides better Resistance vs. Kinetics and Beams, and it has some Resistance vs. Energy Projectiles. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6571</Index>
			<Text>Composite Alloys Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6572</Index>
			<Text>Composite Alloys Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6573</Index>
			<Text>Composite Alloys Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6574</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6575</Index>
			<Text>This armor is very expensive to process, yet is almost as strong as Composite Alloy Armor, while managing to weigh much less. It offers improvment in Kinetic, Beam and Energy Resistances, while have some Explosion Resistance as well. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6576</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6577</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6578</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6579</Index>
			<Text>New generation of Ceramic Armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6580</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6581</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6582</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6583</Index>
			<Text>Bionic Alloys</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6584</Index>
			<Text>Bionic Armor regens when damaged. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6585</Index>
			<Text>Bionic armor is installed externally on ships for protection. It can regenrate itself, repair the ship, and provide turn thrust. It Consumes power and weighs a lot. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6586</Index>
			<Text>Bionic Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6587</Index>
			<Text>Bionic Armor Med</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6588</Index>
			<Text>Bionic Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6589</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Alloys</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6590</Index>
			<Text>Though not strong enough to serve as an external armor, this metal can replace internal bulkheads and help repair the ship when not in combat and also has self regeneartion abilities, even in combat. It has a high power consumption, even when not repairing anything.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6591</Index>
			<Text>Shapememory Alloy can slowly repair itself when damaged. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6592</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6593</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6594</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6595</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6596</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor consumes power and creates small quantities of ordnance for the ship, while also adding some ship repair ability and self regeneration. It also contributes to EMP protection and is somewhat resistant to energy projectiles and beams. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6597</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor won't self repair but slowly regens ammo instead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6598</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6599</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6600</Index>
			<Text>Organic Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6601</Index>
			<Text>Organic Bioplates</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6602</Index>
			<Text>By combining Artificial Organic Material and Previous Bio Armor, we can create a substance with all the characteristics of both materials, while also improving their Energy Weapons and Beam Resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6603</Index>
			<Text>A result of the combined bionic and organic plates. The plate now repairs the whole ship and regenerates ammo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6604</Index>
			<Text>Organic Bioplates Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6605</Index>
			<Text>Organic Bioplates Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6606</Index>
			<Text>Organic Bioplates Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6607</Index>
			<Text>Armored Solarpanel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6608</Index>
			<Text>Armored Solarpanels. Provides some power flow and storage to space ships, at a lower rigidity and slightly higher price. This armor also has an interesting ability to slightly amplify installed shields in ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6609</Index>
			<Text>Armored Solarpanels, provide some to spaceship</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6610</Index>
			<Text>Electro Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6611</Index>
			<Text>Electro Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6612</Index>
			<Text>Electro Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6613</Index>
			<Text>Solar Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6614</Index>
			<Text>This armor improves upon Electro Armor in several ways. It generates more power flow, provides more rigidity, grants more power storage, better amplify installed shields, and it supplies a larger radius of power. It is still, however, less strong than conventional steel armor. It has some resistance to beam weapons, as the collectors need heat in order to provide power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6615</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Armored Solar collector, provides power within a small radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6616</Index>
			<Text>Solar Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6617</Index>
			<Text>Solar Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6618</Index>
			<Text>Solar Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6619</Index>
			<Text>Fairy Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6620</Index>
			<Text>This Armor is the culmination of the best solar armor technology we can create thus far. It is stronger, better amplifies shields, and generates better power flow and power storage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6621</Index>
			<Text>Experimental Shield-Generator Armor. A type of experimental armor, create a small shield nearby. !DRAWN POWER HEAVILY! </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6622</Index>
			<Text>Fairy Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6623</Index>
			<Text>Fairy Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6624</Index>
			<Text>Fairy Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6625</Index>
			<Text>Shield Amp Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6626</Index>
			<Text>This Armor has bvery improved Shield Amplification Technology. It is stronger than Steel Armor, but it costs more, weighs more, and needs power as well. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6627</Index>
			<Text>The mass-produced version of Experimental Electronic Armor-5 Fairy(XSGA5). Greatly reduces energy comsuption and also improves power storage, range, and Shield Amplification.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6628</Index>
			<Text>Ampifier Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6629</Index>
			<Text>Ampifier Armor Med</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6630</Index>
			<Text>Ampifier Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6631</Index>
			<Text>Frontier Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6632</Index>
			<Text>A better Shield Amp Armor, which can also store more power than previous armor. Production costs of this armor are very high, but the benefits are obvious. Vulnerability to Energy projectiles is futher reduced with this technology. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6633</Index>
			<Text>The Frontier Armor is composed of Ceramic Armor, Composite Armor, amd large Shield Amplification module. This makes it very durable, and almost self sustained. The toughness of the armor is somewhere between Ceramic and Composite Armors. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6634</Index>
			<Text>Frontier Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6635</Index>
			<Text>Frontier Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>6636</Index>
			<Text>Frontier Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8001</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8002</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8003</Index>
			<Text>A quickly rotating Gatling Turret. The rotating barrels have increased the number of projectiles that can fire. It also features a 180 degree angle of engagement. Will only fire upon enemy missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8004</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8005</Index>
			<Text>Dual Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8006</Index>
			<Text>Dual Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8007</Index>
			<Text>A larger point defense gatling turret. A high fire rate and an engagement angle of 360 degrees make this the optimal defensive weapon against enemy missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8008</Index>
			<Text>Dual Gatling Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8009</Index>
			<Text>Flak AA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8010</Index>
			<Text>FlakAA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8011</Index>
			<Text>Flak AA Cannons have twice the range of normal PD weapons. A good weapon versus missiles and fighters. They feature a 180 degree fire arc.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8012</Index>
			<Text>FlakAA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8013</Index>
			<Text>Advanced FlakAA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8014</Index>
			<Text>Advanced FlakAA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8015</Index>
			<Text>Advanced FlakAA Cannons are a larger and more powerful rapid fire Flak weapon, capable of targeting fighters. They feature a 360 degree fire arc.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8016</Index>
			<Text>Advanced FlakAA Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8017</Index>
			<Text>XFAA-GreatWall</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8018</Index>
			<Text>XFAA-GreatWall</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8019</Index>
			<Text>Experimental Flak AA Cannon. Engage angle: 270 degree.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8020</Index>
			<Text>XFAA-GreatWall</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8021</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type61 AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8022</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using default AP ammo. +5% damage against armor, but -15% damage against shields. Explosion radius: Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8023</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type61 APFSDS</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8024</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using special APFSDS(Armor-Piercing Fin-Stabilized Discarding-Sabot) ammo. +30% chance of penetrating shields. Explosion radius: None/Low</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8025</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type61 HESH</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8026</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using special HESH(High-Explosive Squash Head) ammo. +20% damage against armor, but -80% damage against shields. Explosion radius: Extra Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8027</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type81</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8028</Index>
			<Text>A very big, double barreled mass driver, using AP ordnance. Its sheer is somewhat effective versus armor, but less effective versus shields. The shots do, however, explode on impact.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8029</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type80</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8030</Index>
			<Text>A very large, double barreled mass driver, using special APFSDS Armor-Piercing Fin-Stabilized Discarding-Sabot) ammo. Its sheer projectile mass has a chance to ignore shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8031</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type74</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8032</Index>
			<Text>A very large mass driver, using special HESH (High-Explosive Squash Head) ammo. It is effective against armor, but less effective against shields. Its explosion radius is very large, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8033</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type90 AP</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8034</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using default AP ammo. +10% damage against armor, but -15% damage against shields. Explosion radius: Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8035</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type90 APFSDS</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8036</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using special APFSDS(Armor-Piercing Fin-Stabilized Discarding-Sabot) ammo. +50% chance to penetrate shields. Explosion radius: None/Low</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8037</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannon Type90 HESH</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8038</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using special HESH(High-Explosive Squash Head) ammo. +40% damage against armor but -75% damage against shields. Explosion radius: Extra Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8039</Index>
			<Text>XAC 0-Loki</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8040</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using default AP ammo. +15% damage against armor, but -15% damage against shields. Explosion radius: Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8041</Index>
			<Text>XAC 1-Behemoth</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8042</Index>
			<Text>Experimental Spring-mount cannons, using special APFSDS(Armor-Piercing Fin-Stabilized Discarding-Sabot) ammo. +50% chance to penetrate shields. Explosion radius: None/Low</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8043</Index>
			<Text>XAC 6-Thor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8044</Index>
			<Text>Spring-mount cannons, using special HESH(High-Explosive Squash Head) ammo. +40% damage against armor but -70% damage against shields. Explosion radius: EXX Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8045</Index>
			<Text>Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8046</Index>
			<Text>A slightly better version of the older Nuclear reactor. It will explode if destroyed, but it provides more power while also being a little sturdier.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8047</Index>
			<Text>Overload Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8048</Index>
			<Text>The overload Fusion reactor produces more power by augmenting its fusion capabilities with other advanced technologies. As a result, its mass and cost are higher, and it is very fragile.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8049</Index>
			<Text>Overload Anti Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8050</Index>
			<Text>The Overload Anti-Matter Reactor will provide 150% more power than a normal one. However, their inherent instability makes them fragile, and they have a small power supply range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8051</Index>
			<Text>Linked Quantum Fusion Reactors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8052</Index>
			<Text>A protective chamber contaning the linked power output of 6 Quantum Fusion Reactors. The chamber is also equipped with a small auxiliary shield and damage control team, allowing it to contribute to ship repairs.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8053</Index>
			<Text>Linked Anti-Matter Reactors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8054</Index>
			<Text>A repurposed hangar containing 6 anti-matter reactors. The hangar comes equipped with a small auxiliary shield and a damage control team that can aid in ship repairs. Beware however, a powerful explosive blast will occur if the hangar is destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8055</Index>
			<Text>Parallel Black hole Reactor Set</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8056</Index>
			<Text>A Parallel Black hole Reactor Set. 6 Connected Plasma Reactors. Huge power output. The reactor hangar is also equipped with a small emergency shield and damage control team, allowing it to self repair. Note however, a massive explosive blast wave will occur if destroyed!</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8057</Index>
			<Text>Cold Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8058</Index>
			<Text>A Cold Fusion Reactor. Very stable, and won't collapse violently. To achieve this, we had to lower its power output, giving it the same energy production as our previous Fusion Reactors. The addition of an enclosed armor shell allows for a safer power output radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8059</Index>
			<Text>Armored Cold Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8060</Index>
			<Text>By sacrificing a small amount of power, we were able to surround this Cold Fusion Reactor in protective armor plates, heavily increasing its durability and almost completely containing the explosion in the case of a structural collapse.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8061</Index>
			<Text>Armored Anti-Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8062</Index>
			<Text>This medium sized Anti-Matter Reactor inside an armor encasing will contain most of the explosion damage from the reactor in the case of its destruction. Unfortunately, due to structural limitations, it is not possible to design larger armored Anti-Matter reactors.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8063</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Tech</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8064</Index>
			<Text>VOB Frigate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8065</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is a massive auxiliary high-speed booster, designed to be installed on the exterior of a ship. It provides massive forward thrust and small warp thrust, but no turn thrust. It also features an integrated shield for self defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8066</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is massive auxiliary high-speed booster. A fast recharge shield has been installed for self protection. Can only be placed on the outside layer of the ship. Due to the high power draw and integrated systems, this module explodes when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8067</Index>
			<Text>VOB Cruisers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8068</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is a massive auxiliary high-speed booster, designed to be installed on the exterior of a ship. It provides massive forward thrust and small warp thrust, but no turn thrust. It also features an integrated shield for self defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8069</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is a massive auxiliary high-speed booster. A fast recharge shield has been installed for self protection. Can only be placed on the outside layer of the ship. Due to the high power draw and integrated systems, this module explodes when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8070</Index>
			<Text>Adv. Colonization</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8071</Index>
			<Text>Industrial I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8072</Index>
			<Text>As our civilization grows, we must find ways to exploit more of our colonies' industrial potentials. Research in this area involves many steps towards the creation of a robust industrial backbone that will maintain our economy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8073</Index>
			<Text>Upgraded Xeno mines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8074</Index>
			<Text>Upgraded Xeno Mines exploit more of the planet's mineral deposits. Their byproducts can be sold in local markets, yielding income.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8075</Index>
			<Text>Industrial II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8076</Index>
			<Text>Developing efficient automation is a crucial step required to push a higher production output from our colonies.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8077</Index>
			<Text>Robotic Factory</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8078</Index>
			<Text>A Robotic Factory. A great technological marvel. These factories use robots for production, and are almost fully automated. They require very little sentient intervention. Products from these factories contribute to the farming industry, providing extra food. Assembled devices allow extra leisure time for the colonists, leading to increased revenue. Unfortunately, byproducts of the huge production lines affect the planet's climate. The factory also aids a little with the ship repair capacity of orbiting ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8079</Index>
			<Text> (-0.75) Fertility On Build, +6 production per turn, +1 food per turn, +15% tax, +100 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8080</Index>
			<Text>Nano Mining</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8081</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Miniature Nanobots will automatically spread out underground, bringing minerals to the surface. Due to environmental effects, they are recommended to be built on mining colonies.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8082</Index>
			<Text> (-0.3) Fertility On Build, +4 production per richness, +30 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8083</Index>
			<Text>Industrial III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8084</Index>
			<Text>This research will make production procedures almost fully automated and can make every colony a main production hub.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8085</Index>
			<Text>Nano Assembly</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8086</Index>
			<Text>An Almost self sufficient updated variant of the Robotic Factory. Its environmental effects are reduced, it contributes to the research industry, and it also frees up some time for colonists to spend at home, increasing consumer revenue.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8087</Index>
			<Text> (-0.2) Fertility On Build, +7 production per turn, +0.25 research per turn, +10% tax</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8091</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Farming II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8092</Index>
			<Text>In order to stay happy and useful, our colonists must have sufficient food on their tables. We must invest in more efficient farming methods to increase food output on each colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8093</Index>
			<Text>Upgraded Xeno Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8094</Index>
			<Text>Upgraded Xeno Farms use even more advanced farming and husbandry techniques on alien soil. Byproducts of Upgraded Xeno Farms can be sold, adding taxable income to the colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8095</Index>
			<Text>VOB Battleship</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8096</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is a massive auxiliary high-speed booster, designed to be installed on the exterior of a ship. It provides massive forward thrust and small warp thrust, but no turn thrust. It also features an integrated shield for self defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8097</Index>
			<Text>VOB Titan</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8098</Index>
			<Text>The Vanguard Over Boost (VOB) is a massive auxiliary high-speed booster, designed to be installed on the exterior of a ship. It provides massive forward thrust and small warp thrust, but no turn thrust. It also features an integrated shield for self defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8099</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurret Type54</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8100</Index>
			<Text>This is a basic, twin barrel Auto Turret designed to operate in vacuum. Its main advantage is that it can be fitted on smaller ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8101</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurret Type62</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8102</Index>
			<Text>A medium sized Auto turret. 3 Barrels, medium to long range, and heavy projectiles. These work well when installed as a group.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8103</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurret Type80</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8104</Index>
			<Text>The heaviest turret that can be practically installed on star ships. It has four barrels and good fire coverage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8105</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Frigate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8106</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrusters are small thrusters installed on the side of a ship. They can significantly increase a ship's turn rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8107</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Cruiser</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8108</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrusters are small thrusters installed on the side of a ship. They can significantly increase a ship's turn rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8109</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust -  Battleship </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8110</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrusters are small thrusters installed on the side of a ship. They can significantly increase a ship's turn rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8111</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Titan</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8112</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrusters are small thrusters installed on the side of a ship. They can significantly increase a ship's turn rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8113</Index>
			<Text>XGC-ForAnswer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8114</Index>
			<Text>The 406mm Exp Gatling Cannon 'ForAnswer(XGC-63)' takes the term 'quantity over quality' to a whole new level, and will quickly turn any ship foolish enough to enter within its range into unrecyclable junk! It also eats through ammunition like it's going out of fashion.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8115</Index>
			<Text>Adv EnergyWeapons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8116</Index>
			<Text>Adv EnergyWeapons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8117</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8118</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Shotgun, suited for close range combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8119</Index>
			<Text>Twin Plasma Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8120</Index>
			<Text>Twin Plasma Shotgun, suited for close range combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8121</Index>
			<Text>Ion Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8122</Index>
			<Text>Ion Shotgun, suited for close range combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8123</Index>
			<Text>Triple Ion Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8124</Index>
			<Text>Triple Ion Shotgun, suited for close range combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8125</Index>
			<Text>Void Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8126</Index>
			<Text>Void Shotgun, suited for close range combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8127</Index>
			<Text>XAVSG-Shattered Skies</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8128</Index>
			<Text>The Experimental Auto Void ShotGun (XAVSG-Shattered Skies) requires a huge amount of power to fire. However, shield generators will barely hold up to the shot.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8129</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Generator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8130</Index>
			<Text>This is an advanced fusion powered fighter generator, combined with some of the new cold fusion tech. It is easier to be cooled in a fighter or corvette frames, therefore it is not available for larger hull types. It is still highly volatile upon destruction.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8131</Index>
			<Text>VOB Fighter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8132</Index>
			<Text>Fighter VOB provides high warp power in combination with a small shield. Due to the high power draw and integrated systems, this module will explode if destroyed. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8133</Index>
			<Text>Fighter ASG Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8134</Index>
			<Text>Having forward firing vulcans on our fighters is useful, but we need superior alternatives with wider fire arcs if we want to make fighters really count in skirmishes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8135</Index>
			<Text>Fighter HASG Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8136</Index>
			<Text>We can improve our fighter turrets by adding superior firepower. These require more efficient vacuum ammunition loading mechanisms. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8137</Index>
			<Text>Fighter QF 17-pdr</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8138</Index>
			<Text>The Fighter Quick-Firing 17-pounder is a 76.2 mm anti-ship cannon that provides our fighters with useful anti ship capabilities.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8139</Index>
			<Text>Fusion Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8140</Index>
			<Text>Fusion Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8141</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8142</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8143</Index>
			<Text>Ion Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8144</Index>
			<Text>Ion Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8145</Index>
			<Text>AntiMatter Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8146</Index>
			<Text>AntiMatter Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8147</Index>
			<Text>Heavy AntiMatter Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8148</Index>
			<Text>Heavy AntiMatter Projector</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8149</Index>
			<Text>XVP-Scarlet Rain</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8150</Index>
			<Text>An experimental void Projector(XVP-Scarlet Rain). just like the name implies, it fires projectile-like rain over targets until they are utterly destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8151</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8152</Index>
			<Text>A Torpedo class weapon mounted on fighters. Due to its smaller size, it has comparatively lower damage and range than capital ship torpedoes, but its usefulness is still apparent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8153</Index>
			<Text>Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8154</Index>
			<Text>Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8155</Index>
			<Text>Light Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8156</Index>
			<Text>Light Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8157</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8158</Index>
			<Text>As our ships grow larger, so too do their munition requirements. We can invest research into more efficient, larger storage modules for our ammunition, allowing for more sustainable firepower.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8159</Index>
			<Text>High Capacity Ammunition Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8160</Index>
			<Text>This facility stores ammunition more efficiently than smaller ammunition storages.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8161</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Fabricator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8162</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Fabricator,ammo regen:5</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8163</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Assembly</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8164</Index>
			<Text>This facility is a dedicated ordnance manufacturing module. Our larger ships will surely benefit from it during drawn out battles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8165</Index>
			<Text>Nano Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8166</Index>
			<Text>With the invention of nanobots, we now have a way to improve all of our storage techniques. These little robots will sort, transport, and assemble any kind of weapon or ammunition required. They will also allow us to construct an efficient Nano Storage structure on our colonies, able to store and sort massive amounts of food and production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8167</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Colony Module</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>8168</Index>
			<Text>This Colony upgrade module will provide a newly founded colony an additional 30 food and production. Very important in the early stages of any colony.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8169</Index>
			<Text>Automated Ammunition Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8170</Index>
			<Text>This Almost fully automated ammunition storage facility is designed for our capital class ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8171</Index>
			<Text>Battle Cruiser</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8172</Index>
			<Text>A Battle Cruiser is an alternative Cruiser design allowing for more weaponry classes to fit within.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8173</Index>
			<Text>Military Base</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8174</Index>
			<Text>Military Bases are another step forward in colony ground defense. This building allows you to train infantry-class troops at your colony just as with Military Outposts, but they are sturdier and pack more of a punch when holding off ground invasions.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8175</Index>
			<Text>Missile Defense III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8176</Index>
			<Text>It would be wise to improve our planetary defenses with weapons that can deter invaders. A series of giant SAM launchers could be a good start.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8177</Index>
			<Text>Planet Fortification</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8178</Index>
			<Text>A fortified area on the planet with trenches, defense emplacements, and planetary shielding generators.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8179</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Defence Platform</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8180</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Defence Platform</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8181</Index>
			<Text>Military Fortress</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8182</Index>
			<Text>Military Fortress "Ikaragu"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8183</Index>
			<Text>Fortress Cruiser Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8184</Index>
			<Text>Fortress Cruiser Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8185</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Plasma Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8186</Index>
			<Text>We can install internal Plasma bomb bays on our Bombers, capable of inflicting heavy damage to enemy ships, especially versus Armor. The number of bombs per module is limited.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8187</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Ion Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8188</Index>
			<Text>We can develop Internal Ion bomb bays on our Bombers. They would be slightly more effective against shields, while also inflicting EMP damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8189</Index>
			<Text>Strike Bomber</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8190</Index>
			<Text>Strike Bomber, "SouRai"</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8191</Index>
			<Text>Assault Battleship</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8192</Index>
			<Text>This massive ship would be great for assaulting planets or breaking through defensive lines. However, it is extremely heavy, thus making it susceptible to flanking.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8193</Index>
			<Text>Assault Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8194</Index>
			<Text>Assault Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8195</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Farming III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8196</Index>
			<Text>We can perfect our farming methods on alien planets in such a way that we will significantly improve our planetary environments, making our colonies flourish. Another step towards truly planet-wide terraforming.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8197</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Xeno Farm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8198</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Xeno Farms expand upon the Upgraded Xeno Farm technology, enabling the construction of massive farms that produce more food, and less byproducts. A drawback is less income from byproduct market sales.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8199</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8200</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8201</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8202</Index>
			<Text>Very strong, resistant to Energy Projectiles and Beam. Creates ordnance, turn thrust, has EMP protection, self regenerates, and repairs the ship. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8203</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Med</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8204</Index>
			<Text>repair:120, ammo gen:0.75, EMP res:4500</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8205</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Bionic Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8206</Index>
			<Text>repair:210, ammo gen:1.2, EMP res:9800</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8207</Index>
			<Text>Small Torpedo Tube</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8208</Index>
			<Text>This torpedo tube launches slow-moving but devastating torpedoes, packed to the hilt with explosives.  They require substantial ordnance to fire and can be intercepted by point defense weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8209</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8210</Index>
			<Text>Crystal Shield Amplification Armor. Provides more Shield Amplification. The Crystals in this armor are processed and designed to "Streamline" hyper space travel, boosting Warp speed. It also stores abit more power. Cost is high. Energy Cannon vulnerability is minimized.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8211</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8212</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active Armor is a thorough blend of all our knowledge in Solid State Armor Technology. The mass is slightly higher than the already very light Crystal armor, but it fares well against most known damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8213</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8214</Index>
			<Text>Streamlined for hyper space, powerful shield Amplification module, and the toughest underlying armor in this series of technology. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8215</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8216</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8217</Index>
			<Text>Mirage Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8218</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8219</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8220</Index>
			<Text>A blend of all Solid Armor plates. It reacts with most attack types and reduces their damage. It offers improvments in Resistance over all armor of lower tiers. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8221</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8222</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8223</Index>
			<Text>Hyper-Active Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8224</Index>
			<Text></Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8225</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedo II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8226</Index>
			<Text>An improved version of the previous Fighter Torpedo. Slightly more damage, and faster.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8227</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Anti Matter Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8228</Index>
			<Text>Anti Matter bomb bays can inflict heavy damage upon enemy capital ships. The bombs are powerful, but have no special abilities beyond their pure destructiveness.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8229</Index>
			<Text>Phased Rapid Energy Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8230</Index>
			<Text>This deadly turret has a medium to long range, and can fire rapid high energy projectiles which will bypass shields half of the times. It will also deal increased damage to armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8231</Index>
			<Text>Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8232</Index>
			<Text>Representatives within The Energy Research branch believe they can now use current energy military knowledge to construct fast-tracking Energy Point Defense weapons, useful for intercepting incoming anti-ship enemy missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8233</Index>
			<Text> Advanced Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8234</Index>
			<Text>We can now create Point Defense "Laser" projectiles that will pack more punch against incoming missiles, while retaining the same projectile speed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8235</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk2</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8236</Index>
			<Text>An improved version of our kinetic platform cannons, now featuring even higher range, faster projectiles, and more damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8237</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8238</Index>
			<Text>Our most advanced orbital platform weapon yet. With the extreme range, fast projectile speed, and long reload times, some have come to calling them orbital sniper cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8239</Index>
			<Text>Orbital Kinetic Cannon Mk1</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8240</Index>
			<Text>A high performance twin Kinetic Cannon, specially designed for small and heavy platforms in high orbit around a planet. It features a high range, and the 360 degree swivel allows for the maximum field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8241</Index>
			<Text>Small Sensor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>8242</Index>
			<Text>Information in war is most crucial, with that mindset long range sensors were developed. Equiping a ship with a sensor module increases its detection range to 22 000 units.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Overdrive -->
		<Token>
			<Index>10003</Index>
			<Text>Automatic Factory</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10004</Index>
			<Text>The Automated Factory is a marvel of engineering, working almost completely without sentient intervention, and remaining environmentally friendly. It also adds storage to the colony, and doubles the ship repair capacity of the colony for orbiting ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10005</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Customs Station</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10006</Index>
			<Text>The planetary customs station maintains a small fleet of vessels that board and inspect all ships moving throughout the system. This ensures that all customs and taxes are paid. It also adds some storage space.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10007</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Network Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10008</Index>
			<Text>The GalNet is a computer network spanning your entire empire, using specialized satellites and passing ships to carry information across the vast gulfs between the stars. Not only does it give access to staggering amounts of silly animal pictures, it also improves research and commerce on any planet connected to it.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10009</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Stock Exchange</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10010</Index>
			<Text>The Galactic Stock Exchange is the central place where stocks of galactic mega-corporations are traded. The proceeds can be taxed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10011</Index>
			<Text>Geo Survey Satellite Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10012</Index>
			<Text>The Geo Survey Satellite Network measures changes in the density of the planet's crust, allowing for the easy detection of all major ore veins. It is mostly suited and cost effective for planets with high richness.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10013</Index>
			<Text>Hive City</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10014</Index>
			<Text>This incredibly massive, highly advanced structure will provide room for 4 billion population. Due to the extreme amount of land and resources required for construction, planetary fertility will be moderately reduced.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10015</Index>
			<Text>Livestock Cloning Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10016</Index>
			<Text>Instead of the common breeding programs of the past, this building clones meat from various races of xeno livestock, taking advantage of the best genetic attributes. It produces less food than Xeno Farms, but maintenance is very low. Thanks to healthier meat, more ethical lifestyles, and more land available for crops, population growth slightly increases.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10017</Index>
			<Text>Luxury Resort</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10018</Index>
			<Text>A luxurious resort for the very-well-off. Provides a significant boost to planetary commerce.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10019</Index>
			<Text>Particle Accelerator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10020</Index>
			<Text>A particle accelerator, as the name implies, accelerates particles to nearly the speed of light, smashing them together at relativistic speeds to find new information about the makeup of the universe. Provides 1 point of research per scientist. Rumors of the potential for an irreversible black hole consumption event caused by this device are likely greatly exaggerated.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10021</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Stock Exchange</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10022</Index>
			<Text>The Planetary Stock exchange allows stocks of planetary companies to be traded. This improves commerce on the planet and thus tax revenue.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10023</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Supercomputer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10024</Index>
			<Text>While advances in miniaturization have made computers smaller, they may inversely allow computers to be scaled up almost indefinitely. Set into the planetary crust, this gigantic computer can crunch almost unimaginable amounts of data, helping scientists immensely. Provides a flat +1 per turn research bonus to any colony, and increases production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10025</Index>
			<Text>Plant Genetic Manipulation Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10026</Index>
			<Text>This building adapts local and foreign flora to grow better within a planet's individual climates, promoting greater yields. Thus, larger areas of the planet can sustain agriculture, in effect improving the fertility level.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10027</Index>
			<Text>Soil Enrichment Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10028</Index>
			<Text>In an attempt to improve agricultural output, the planet's soil is enriched to support plant growth, increasing fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10031</Index>
			<Text>System Research Network Uplink</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10032</Index>
			<Text>The System Research Network links all research labs, universities and test centers in a system together, allowing scientists to communicate and cooperate easily, limited only by the speed of light.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10033</Index>
			<Text>Weather Manipulation Center</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10034</Index>
			<Text>Using advanced computers and a network of specialized satellites, this buildings monitors the global weather and directs measures to manipulate it to improve plant growth. This increases the average fertility of the planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10035</Index>
			<Text>Zero Gravity Production Plant</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10036</Index>
			<Text>Certain advanced alloys cannot be produced under conditions of gravity. Orbital production plants allow fabrication in zero gravity, increasing productivity, and aiding the repair capacity of orbiting ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10037</Index>
			<Text>Livestock Cloning</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10038</Index>
			<Text>Rather than raising whole animals for meat, this facility will grant us the ability to efficiently clone edible meat to exact specifications, eliminating the need for slaughterhouses and freeing up vast tracks of land. This will improve the food supply of the colony and promote a growing population.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10039</Index>
			<Text>Hive Cities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10040</Index>
			<Text>Specifically designed to house as many people as possible, Hive Cities rise high above the planet's surface, providing housing for 4 billion people. Each home is fitted with advanced holographic emitters and spacial distortion fields, allowing people to comfortably live in an incredibly small area, with as much freedom as they could possibly desire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10041</Index>
			<Text>Soil Enrichment</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10042</Index>
			<Text>Combining artificial and natural fertilizer, we can improve a planet's fertility to increase agricultural output.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10043</Index>
			<Text>Plant Genetic Manipulation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10044</Index>
			<Text>By manipulating local and alien plants, we can adapt them to the environment to grow better and yield more. In effect, this increases a planet's fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10045</Index>
			<Text>Weather Manipulation</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10046</Index>
			<Text>By manipulating a planet's climate, we can decrease devastating weather effects while preserving the optimal conditions for plant growth. In effect, this increases a planet's fertility.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10047</Index>
			<Text>Geo Survey</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10048</Index>
			<Text>We can create a network of satellites that will help discover new ore veins, whereas with conventional detection methods they would ordinarily be overlooked.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10049</Index>
			<Text>Zero Gravity Production</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10050</Index>
			<Text>Certain advanced alloys can only be produced in zero gravity. We can now build facilities that exploit microgravity for production.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10051</Index>
			<Text>Asteroid Tracking</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10052</Index>
			<Text>Even the star systems without extensive asteroid belts still receive the occasional visitor. With this technology, we can track and mine these passing asteroids.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10053</Index>
			<Text>Automatic Production</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10054</Index>
			<Text>Using advancements in computing and industrial robot design, we can create a factory that produces goods almost completely without intervention.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10055</Index>
			<Text>System Networks</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10056</Index>
			<Text>While linking computers together seems fairly simple on a planet, it is quite a bit more difficult between planets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10057</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Computing</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10058</Index>
			<Text>Using new discoveries in chip design, we can create a supercomputer capable of crunching incredible amounts of data.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10059</Index>
			<Text>Particle Accelerator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10060</Index>
			<Text>The last remaining questions about the origin of the universe can be answered by taking the smallest parts of it and smashing them together.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10061</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Networks</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10062</Index>
			<Text>If connecting planets of a system together was difficult, transferring data between systems will be even harder. With this technology, we can now finally open high data transfer in the GalNet. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10063</Index>
			<Text>Imperial Customs</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10064</Index>
			<Text>Trade between planets must be regulated to protect the local economies, avoid ecological contamination, and, most of all, to ensure that the state get its cut of all proceeds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10065</Index>
			<Text>Planetary Stock Trade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10066</Index>
			<Text>Any planetary government seeking to stimulate economic growth would be well-advised to create a place where companies can find investors. The increase in tax revenue is just a bonus.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10067</Index>
			<Text>Luxury Resorts</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10068</Index>
			<Text>The more planets we explore, the more areas we find that lend themselves well to tourism. Building a resort allows the very wealthy to spend their money in one of these beautiful havens.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10069</Index>
			<Text>Galactic Stock Trade</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10070</Index>
			<Text>The level of revenue exchange our galactic mega-corporations require is far beyond the scope of what one planet can accommodate. It would be wise to create a single place in our empire where these corporations can meet with investors. It would be equally wise to tax them for it.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10071</Index>
			<Text>+30% Tax Efficiency, +20 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10072</Index>
			<Text>+2 credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10073</Index>
			<Text>+0.1 research per assigned colonist, +0.25 Flat Research, +20% Tax</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10074</Index>
			<Text> (-0.5) Fertility on build +4 planet population, +100 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10075</Index>
			<Text>+10 Production per turn, +100 Storage, aids in ship repair</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10076</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 food per assigned colonist, +0.05 population per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10077</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 flat Research, +0.25 research and credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>10078</Index>
			<Text>+3 production per richness</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10079</Index>
			<Text> (+0.3) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10080</Index>
			<Text>(+0.1) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10081</Index>
			<Text> (+0.5) fertility on build</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10082</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 production per assigned colonist, +20 storage, aids in ship repair</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10095</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Vernier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10096</Index>
			<Text>A basic module that allows for the control of a small craft's direction.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10110</Index>
			<Text>Having developed nuclear-thermal engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small craft. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10113</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Nuclear Thermal</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10117</Index>
			<Text>Having developed Plasma Torch engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small crafts. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10119</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Plasma Torch</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10123</Index>
			<Text>Having developed Antimatter engines, we can now adapt the smallest version to provide attitude control for our small crafts. This increases their maneuverability.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10125</Index>
			<Text>Turn Thrust - Antimatter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10165</Index>
			<Text>This power plant works on the principle of nuclear fission. A containment breach will lead to a rapid irradiation of large portions of the surrounding area, which usually means the ship would have to be scuttled.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10166</Index>
			<Text>Massive Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10167</Index>
			<Text>Large Nuclear Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10177</Index>
			<Text>This power plant works on the principle of matter-antimatter annihilation. Its power output is similar to the Overload Fusion Reactor, but at less cost, and more rigidity. A containment breach will lead to a violent explosion.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10178</Index>
			<Text>Massive Antimatter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10180</Index>
			<Text>Medium Antimatter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10217</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10218</Index>
			<Text>These enormous guns can run the entire length of a frigate, giving even our smaller ships a fairly hefty punch that will threaten ships twice their size.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10219</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10220</Index>
			<Text>This enormous gun runs the entire length of a cruiser, giving any ship featuring it a fairly hefty punch.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10221</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10222</Index>
			<Text>This enormous gun runs the entire length of a battleship. It can deliver a devastating blow to any ship foolish enough to cross before its bow.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10223</Index>
			<Text>Titan Spinal Mass Driver</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10224</Index>
			<Text>This gun is the absolute last word regarding any kind of enemy. Larger by itself than many frigates, it can destroy certain ships in only a single hit.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10279</Index>
			<Text>This armor is made up of Liquid Crystals. These are made to flow into any breach and harden in seconds, allowing the armor to repair itself in moments. This gives it unprecedented durability, granting 20% better protection by mass compared to Ceramic Composite Armor. Needs power to function.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10280</Index>
			<Text>Medium Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10281</Index>
			<Text>Small Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10282</Index>
			<Text>Large Liquid Crystal Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10290</Index>
			<Text>Sanitation Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10291</Index>
			<Text>Sanitation buildings reduce the fatalities from natural diseases, improving lifespans for the colony. The maintenance of these structures costs progressively more as the colony grows.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10292</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 population, +0.01 population growth</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10293</Index>
			<Text>Education Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10294</Index>
			<Text>Educating future scientists and engineers is the key to our empire's survival. However, the larger a colony gets, the more it costs.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10295</Index>
			<Text>+0.1 production and +0.2 research per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10296</Index>
			<Text>Transportation Infrastructure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10297</Index>
			<Text>By investing in the transportation network of a planet, production can be made more efficient.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10298</Index>
			<Text>+0.3 production per colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10325</Index>
			<Text>Large Ordnance Storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10326</Index>
			<Text>A scaled-up version of the Medium Ordnance Storage, this module holds more ammunition and is more cost effective.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10333</Index>
			<Text>Medium Cargo Hold</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10334</Index>
			<Text>Advances in ship design and material science allow for much larger cargo holds to be constructed. This one holds 5 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10335</Index>
			<Text>Large Cargo Hold</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10336</Index>
			<Text>Advances in ship design and material science allow for much larger cargo holds to be constructed. This one holds 15 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10337</Index>
			<Text>Container Deck</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10338</Index>
			<Text>Rather than redesigning the cargo hold, this new approach aims to redesign the cargo. By placing it in standardized, self-sufficient containers, we can maximize the amount of cargo carried. This container deck carries 10 containers for a combined storage of 22 units of food, production or frozen colonists.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10344</Index>
			<Text>Imperial University</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10345</Index>
			<Text>Bringing together the best and brightest of our Empire will give huge benefits to research and engineering. In one place, our scientists and engineers can cooperate without the barrier of distance. Only one Imperial University can be built per empire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10346</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 research, +0.1 production per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10551</Index>
			<Text>A clever combination of solar panels and steel frames allows for a system that provides power while simultaneously shielding the modules behind it. Provides 25% less armor strength per mass than conventional steel armor and has to be placed on the outside of the ship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10552</Index>
			<Text>Medium Armored Solar Panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10553</Index>
			<Text>Small Armored Solar Panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>10554</Index>
			<Text>Large Armored Solar panel</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tsun -->
		<Token>
			<Index>13385</Index>
			<Text>Honor-less Scum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13386</Index>
			<Text>Scum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>3387</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hull Reinforcement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>3388</Index>
			<Text>Using new breakthroughs in hull reinforcement and super structure, the Tsunari have developed this substantially larger freighter.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dauntless -->
		<Token>
			<Index>12001</Index>
			<Text>Steel HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12002</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Steel Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12003</Index>
			<Text>Kinetic Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12004</Index>
			<Text>This general-purpose cannon turret fires kinetic projectiles at high velocity that deal significant damage upon impact. Ideal against armoured targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12005</Index>
			<Text>Solar Array</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12006</Index>
			<Text>Solar Panels harvest energy from stars to supplement a ships main power core.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12007</Index>
			<Text>Class I MagShield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12008</Index>
			<Text>Whilst only capable of withstanding a few hits, Magnetic fields are able to cover a wide area and are restored rapidly. This makes them ideal for drawn out skirmishes with smaller ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12009</Index>
			<Text>Medium Overdrive Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12010</Index>
			<Text>This frigate engine has been pushed to the limit, using twice as much power to deliver an additional 50% thrust.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12011</Index>
			<Text>Auxiliary Power Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12012</Index>
			<Text>All-in-one power diagnostics unit. Provides and stores power as well as increasing warp speed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12013</Index>
			<Text>Twin Small Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12014</Index>
			<Text>Coupling multiple engines allows core components to be shared, reducing weight and power usage without a loss to maximum thrust. This does make it easier to disable, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12017</Index>
			<Text>Micro Warp Core</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12018</Index>
			<Text>This external engine channels energy directly from the central warp core and is able to boost a ships speed a significant amount, at both warp and sublight speeds. Unfortunately, safety standards require that this engine design cannot be used for maneuvering; this is to avoid the unfortunate possibility of the ship tearing itself to pieces.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12019</Index>
			<Text>Solar Plate</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12020</Index>
			<Text>Solar Panels harvest energy from stars to supplement a ships main power core. This variant is mounted on a Steel Armour Plate to maximize ship defense. </Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12021</Index>
			<Text>Static Barrier</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12022</Index>
			<Text>Placed on the outside of a ship's hull, these units are charged slowly until they form a powerful, albeit highly localized electromagnetic shield.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12023</Index>
			<Text>Jump Drive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12024</Index>
			<Text>Putting recent innovations in warp theory to work, this drive is capable of traversing systems in mere seconds. While its speed puts conventional drives to shame, it is incredibly power hungry and must be recharged in-between jumps. The structural integrity of this module is very unstable. It is advised to protect it with armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12025</Index>
			<Text>Gunships</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12026</Index>
			<Text>Gunships are a specialized range of lighter Frigates. They are designed to carry a vast array of weaponry, but are often easily destroyed due to their lack of armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12027</Index>
			<Text>Small Inertial Damper</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12998</Index>
			<Text>This Class V shield is a sturdier improvement of the Class III shields. It also costs more, weighs more, and needs more power to function.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>12999</Index>
			<Text>Armored Heavy Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13000</Index>
			<Text>This is a better armored and more powerful canopy generator. Its power draw is exceptionally high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>13001</Index>
			<Text>Improved Canopy Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17402</Index>
			<Text>Gunboat</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17403</Index>
			<Text>BioArmor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17404</Index>
			<Text>Electroplate Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17405</Index>
			<Text>Advanced storage and food preservation techniques allow for massive storage upgrades on our colonies. An extra 500 food and production can be stored in this hi-tech structure's warehouses.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17406</Index>
			<Text>+0.25 research per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17407</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 research per turn, +0.2 production per assigned colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17408</Index>
			<Text>+0.75 food per assigned colonist, +50 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17409</Index>
			<Text>+1 food per assigned colonist, +2 Flat Food, +75 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17410</Index>
			<Text> +1 production per assigned colonist, +50 storage</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced Missile Armor -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17411</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Missile Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17412</Index>
			<Text>We have perfected a new technology to further increase the survivability of our missile-based weaponry by protecting them with advanced armor plating.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17413</Index>
			<Text>Advanced ECM</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced ECM Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17414</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Electronic Counter Measures can further confuse enemy point defense sensors into missing their targets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planet Fortification Building-->
		<Token>
			<Index>17415</Index>
			<Text>We are able to fortify an area on colonized planets which will make ground invasion and orbit bombing harder.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17416</Index>
			<Text>Defensive Building; +1000 Planetary Shields, 2 injuries to each invading troop</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energy pd 2x2 module -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17417</Index>
			<Text>Energy Point Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17418</Index>
			<Text>A Single barreled, energy point defense turret. Created in mind of the constantly growing danger of guided weapons. It has rather low damage, but is accurate and fast firing.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energy pd 3x3 module -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17419</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Energy Point Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17420</Index>
			<Text>An improvement of the basic energy point defense turret. While bigger, it has two barrels, improved rate of fire, and more damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cloud Peak Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17421</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Range Missile Defense</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planetary AutoCannon Emplacement Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17422</Index>
			<Text>Fires auto cannon shells into orbit</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Planetary Sniper Cannon Emplacement Short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17423</Index>
			<Text>Fires high speed shells into orbit</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Military Base descripsion -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17424</Index>
			<Text>This military facility provides a barracks, armory, mess, firing range, and other facilities needed to train and equip infantry for ground combat. It is more advanced than the military outpost.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- System defence torpedo short descripsion -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17425</Index>
			<Text>Fires long range, very rigid torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Velocity stimulance description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17426</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters, more integrated systems for frigates, and Nuclear Thermal thrusters for improved turn rates.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17427</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for cruisers, new cruiser turn thrusters for improved turn rates, and a new jump drive design.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17428</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for battleships, more advanced jump drives, and a plasma torch thruster.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17429</Index>
			<Text>As our control over the galaxy grows, we must improve our hyperspace and subspace travel times. We are focusing on external thrusters and more integrated systems for titans, advanced jump theory, and antimatter thrusters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter ASG turrets description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17430</Index>
			<Text>Anti-ship Gatling (ASG) turrets will increase fighter effectiveness in the battlefield. It is essentially a vulcan cannon mounted on a turret for better field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter HASG turrets description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17431</Index>
			<Text>These Heavy Anti-Ship Gatling turrets can almost double the projectile amount per burst, and use larger ammunition for higher damage. All of this on a better turret with wider field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Nano mining tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17432</Index>
			<Text>Using our knowledge in Nano Machinery, we can create Nano Mining Bots. These tiny machines will save a lot of time and effort ordinarily wasted by transporting and drilling in conventional mining operations.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced solar armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17433</Index>
			<Text>Provides power flow, power radius, and power storage within the ship. Not as strong as steel armor, and much more expensive. It also has an improved Shield Amplification technology.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Ceramic Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17434</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic Armor can withstand a little more punishment than Reactive Armor, but the true benefit is the decrease in mass. Ceramic Armor is very effective vs. Beams and Energy projectiles, and somewhat effective vs. Energy Projectiles. It is also more expensive than Reactive Armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Composite Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17435</Index>
			<Text>Breakthroughs in Chemistry allow for the design and construction of armors twice as strong as steel, with improvements all arcoss the board.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Crystal Armor  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17436</Index>
			<Text>Purple Crystals are almost as tough as Composite Alloys Armor. We can create armor from these purple crystals, but processing it will be highly expensive. The result would be a very strong armor, with reduced mass, and adding explosion resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced FighterShields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17437</Index>
			<Text>For our fighters to survive in an ever more advanced battlefield, better shields will be needed. We can link two shield generators together, creating an overall stronger shield.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cold Fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17438</Index>
			<Text>Cold fusion is a type of nuclear reaction that would occur at, or near room temperature. This is in contrast with "hot" fusion, which takes place naturally within stars, and under immense pressure.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Shield Armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17439</Index>
			<Text>Breakthroughs in shield amplification lead us to much better amplification in these armors, at the cost of some power draw. We managed to negate some of the previous vulnerability to energy projectiles, but it still remains an issue.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- fairy tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17440</Index>
			<Text>Using knowledge gained from previous Solar Armor, we can reach energy production higher than 50% of Nuclear Reactors within a new armor. The code name given for this project is "Fairy". These also have increased shield amplification.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Assault raiders tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17441</Index>
			<Text>We can construct even bigger hangars to launch small frigate size crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Ion Bomb tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17442</Index>
			<Text>This dedicated bomber module launches a barrage of unguided, low accuracy space bombs. The bombs cause EMP damage, and are slightly more effective versus shields, but less effective versus armor. Launches 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Plasma Bomb tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17443</Index>
			<Text>This module launches a barrage of unguided, low accuracy space bombs. The hot plasma is highly effective versus armor. This module fires 4 bomb per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- parallel ion reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17444</Index>
			<Text>Linked Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17445</Index>
			<Text>By repurposing the open space of a hangar bay, we should be able to safely chain together multiple anti-matter reactors, increasing the efficiency of their overall energy output. The hangar might not be very protective, but it's the best our engineers could come up with.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Star lancers tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17446</Index>
			<Text>We can construct and maintain very large bays for frigate support.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter generators tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17447</Index>
			<Text>Since fighters offer limited space for systems, our scientists recommend investing research into a high output fusion generator, tailored specifically for fighter skirmishes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17448</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Cold Fusion Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Cold Fusion Reactor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17449</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Anti-Matter Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Plasma Reactor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fusion reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17450</Index>
			<Text>In a fusion reactor, the principle is that neutrons generated from Deuterium-Tritium fusion reactions will be absorbed into a blanket containing lithium, which surrounds the core. The lithium is then transformed into tritium (which is used to fuel the reactor) and helium. </Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored shields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17451</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve our Class III shields' output and add Ceramic armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17452</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve our Canopy shields' output and add Ceramic armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter torpedos tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17453</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17454</Index>
			<Text>We can now install Torpedo class weapons on fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17455</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Fighters</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Heavy bomber tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17456</Index>
			<Text>We can develop a new fighter hull type. This fighter will have more internal modules for heavier anti-ship bomb loads.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter high calibers (pdr) tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17457</Index>
			<Text>Fighter High Calibers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17458</Index>
			<Text>We can increase fighter battlefield effectiveness by designing better anti-ship cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- ordnance assembly  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17459</Index>
			<Text>Ordnance Facilities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17460</Index>
			<Text>We can design dedicated workshops for ordnance fabrication on capital ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- anti capital missiles  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17461</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Missiles I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17462</Index>
			<Text>We can create missile systems specifically dedicated to destroying enemy capital ships, armed with a warhead capable of efficiently damage armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- dual anti capital missiles  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17463</Index>
			<Text>Anti Capital Missiles II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17464</Index>
			<Text>We can improve our Anti Capital Ship Missiles by making more powerful warheads at destroying armour.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighters ATCSM  tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17465</Index>
			<Text>We can develop technologies that will allow Anti Capital Ship Missiles to be installed on smaller crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighters Torpedos tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17466</Index>
			<Text>We can develop technologies for smaller torpedoes to be installed on fighter craft.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17467</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17468</Index>
			<Text>Further technological improvements for fighter torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17469</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Torpedoes II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Gatling defense tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17470</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Defense I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17471</Index>
			<Text>Improving ship Anti-Missile defense systems may limit the loss of life for our ships and crews. We can look into upgrading the previous Phalanx point defense cannons with better radar and more firepower.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17472</Index>
			<Text>Gatling Defense II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17473</Index>
			<Text>With reliable space-based gatling technology finally complete, we should strive for more firepower against the increasing threat of missiles in the battlefield. A larger defense platform will allow us to accomplish this.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Auto Turrets tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17474</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurrets are large, mass driver guns with wide firing angles. They are designed to overwhelm enemy ships with many fast projectiles. Progression in this field involves the design of larger, more powerful turrets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17475</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17476</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17477</Index>
			<Text>Auto Turrets III</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Flak AA tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17478</Index>
			<Text>Defense Guns I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17479</Index>
			<Text>We can adapt our old air defense weapons for usage in space. These flak turrets will now be capable of targeting fighters, in addition to missiles. Future versions of this weapon will require our engineers to create a larger firing platform.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17480</Index>
			<Text>Defense Guns II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17481</Index>
			<Text>Now that we have a working practice of installing the smaller Flak AA Cannons, our scientists have been able to devise a larger, more powerful platform, perfect for missile and fighter defense on our larger ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Shapemomory armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17482</Index>
			<Text>Advancements in material science now allow us to construct a Shape Memory Metal. This metal will repair itself and other parts of the ship, given enough time. This material also possesses a unique explosive resistance, making it a useful interior bulkhead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Bionic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17483</Index>
			<Text>Bionic alloys can be used to construct a truly unique armor. Slightly stronger than Steel, it can repair the ship, self regenerate, and provide small turn trust through miniature gyroscopic effects in the Bionic Network. It is more expensive than ShapeMemory Alloys, and consumes some power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Organic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17484</Index>
			<Text>We can create an interesting artificial, very hard, but light, organic material. It draws power to maintain functionality, but possesses many special attributes. It is somewhat resistant to energy weapons and beams, thanks to its natural ability to reshape itself. This ability means it can produce ordnance as well. It also has some energy and EMP resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Organic Bioplate armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17485</Index>
			<Text>Combined Organic and Bio Armor. Although less strong than Organic Armor, it has many useful characteristics. It repairs and creates ordnance for the ship, provides turn thrust, self regenerates, and grants EMP protection. The drawback is that it consumes a lot of power. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Adcanved Bionic armor tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17486</Index>
			<Text>This is the most advanced Material we can create in this series of technology. It has all of the Organic Bioplate characteristics, along with some improvements. We have finally turned one of its weaknesses into a strength. Not only is it now much stronger, but its hunger for power is so great, that it has become very resistant to destructive energy beams or projctiles. The cost is very high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- ammo capacity II tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17487</Index>
			<Text>With advancements in AI sorting networks and improved infrastructure, we are able to further perfect the efficiency of our ordnance carrying ship modules. They now support greater ammunition per container than we had ever thought possible, and are mostly automated.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17488</Index>
			<Text>After completely eliminating all manual intervention and maintenance, our ammunition management centers have become completely self contained. By incorporating ammunition drones and robots, the AI seems to utilize advanced logistics needed for the constant flow of ammunition in these very large ship modules. We no longer understand exactly how the AI functions, but it is extremely efficient.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17489</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17490</Index>
			<Text>Ammunition Capacity III</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- assault cannons tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17491</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannons</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17492</Index>
			<Text>We can develop even larger cannons than the massive cannons, designed specifically for Battleships and Titans. They will consume massive amounts of ordnance, but will inflict massive damage as well. </Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- parallel plasma reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17493</Index>
			<Text>Linked Quantum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17494</Index>
			<Text>By linking the output of our quantum fusion reactors, we can ensure their protection within a small space, and amplify their power output through intuned modulation. They will be protected by their encasing and the addition of a local shielding generator.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Extreme  reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17495</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17496</Index>
			<Text>If we are willing to take the risk, we can construct a higher power flow Fusion Reactor, but at increased mass and cost.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17497</Index>
			<Text>Extreme Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17498</Index>
			<Text>We are now able to control an advanced magnetic field that can contain multiple, smaller size Anti-Matter reactions. If we are willing to take the risk, we can construct a higher power flow Anti-Matter Reactor that will utilize this newer, more advanced magnetic field. If destroyed, the resulting explosion will be devastating.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored plasma reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17499</Index>
			<Text>Armored Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Hyper Acceleration reactors tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17500</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Acceleration</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17501</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Acceleration can use advanced, massive magnetic coils to accelerate solid projectiles to relativistic speeds, once thought impossible for such amounts of mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- XGC tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17502</Index>
			<Text>Multi Barrel Drivers</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17503</Index>
			<Text>We can create heavy, multi barreled cannons, assuming you care more for mass drivers than energy.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- advanced fighter shields tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17504</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Shields II</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- cold fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17505</Index>
			<Text>Cold Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- pulse capacitor small description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17506</Index>
			<Text>Pulse Capacitor - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17507</Index>
			<Text>This is a smaller version of the capacitor, meant for ships with limited space. It is less efficient, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Quantum Fusion Tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17508</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17509</Index>
			<Text>Quantum mechanics concerns the physical phenomena of the smallest scales known. Taking advantage of many tiny changes in quantum energy, this reactor is able to generate power. The variations in energy produced by these reactors is very predictable, making them quite stable. Because of this, they can be built on scales larger than any other reactors thus far.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Quantum Fusion Modules description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17510</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17511</Index>
			<Text>This is a Fighter version of the Quantum Fusion Reactor. It produces less energy than an Anti-Matter Fighter reactor, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17512</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17513</Index>
			<Text>This is the medium version of the Quantum Fusion Reactor. It produces less energy than Anti-Matter medium reactors, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17514</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17515</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor produces less energy than Anti-Matter Fighter reactor, costs more, and weighs more. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to its Anti-matter equivalent.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17516</Index>
			<Text>Quantum Fusion Reactor Massive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17517</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor is the biggest single reactor we can build thus far. Its weight and cost is very high. Its major strength, however, is that its explosive force is much weaker in comparison to Anti-matter technology.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Massive Anti_Matter tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17518</Index>
			<Text>Massive Anti-Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17519</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct an incredibly powerful, very large Anti-Matter Reactor. The amount of Anti-Matter stored within is extremely volatile, and should the reactor be destroyed, a powerful explosion will no doubt take place.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored anti-Matter reactor tech name -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17520</Index>
			<Text>Armored Cold Fusion</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored quantum Fusion tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17521</Index>
			<Text>Armored Quantum</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17522</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Quantum Fusion Reactors in decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Cold Fusion Reactor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armored quantum Fusion reactor description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17523</Index>
			<Text>Armored Quantum Fusion Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17524</Index>
			<Text>This Quantum Fusion Reactor has protective armor to contain most of the blast in case of a reactor explosion.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dark-Matter tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17525</Index>
			<Text>Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17526</Index>
			<Text>Although still a mystery to even our greatest minds, this invisible material can be coalesced into small areas. To accomplish this, gigantic, advanced gravitational machines pull ordinary matter apart over vast distances, making way for the dark matter to seep into a proverbial bucket of gravitational potential. By then surrounding and compressing it, usable energy is continuously emitted, making for an incredibly reliable source of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17527</Index>
			<Text>Dark Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17528</Index>
			<Text>This reactor will provide high and stable energy for our ships. Other sizes of Dark Matter reactor are not produced, due the the standardized way the dark matter is collected.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- heavy nuclear bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17529</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Nuclear Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17530</Index>
			<Text>This bomb bay can utilize very powerful Tactical or Strategic Nuclear payloads to bombard enemy colonies. It has a high destructive potential. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- bio terminator bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17531</Index>
			<Text>BioTerminator Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17532</Index>
			<Text>Organic molecules, even those from different worlds, all share many commonalities. By aggressively attacking those common roots, we have created a bomb that will very rapidly and thoroughly kill anything it comes in contact with. A few of these bombs will unquestionably destroy an entire civilian population in short order. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- anti matter bomb description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17533</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17534</Index>
			<Text>This highly destructive bomb turns everything caught in its explosion radius into gamma rays. Very efficient for clearing out enemy colonies. The target planet will suffer a temporary reduction to its Fertility level. Constant bombing might permanently reduce fertility and even change the planet's climate forever.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Tritanium Armor Tech description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17535</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17536</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor is three times stronger than Steel Armor. Though the existence of this material was already previously known, its mass was not yet practical for ships. With our knowledge in Hyper-Active Armor, we can now design low mass Tritanium armor. The cost is very high.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17537</Index>
			<Text>The ultimate armor. The strongest material known for its mass/strength ratio. It also nullifies the effect of Armor Piercing III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17538</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17539</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17540</Index>
			<Text>Tritanium Armor Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- mass driver_short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17541</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Short</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17542</Index>
			<Text>This version of the Mass Driver has a shorter barrel, made to fit into smaller ships. Its projectiles have shorter range and less explosion radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17543</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Dual</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17544</Index>
			<Text>The Dual Mass Driver features a dual cannon deployment, each cannon sporting larger barrels that pack more of a punch.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- armored dark matter  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17545</Index>
			<Text>Armored Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17546</Index>
			<Text>We are able to envelop our Dark Matter Reactors with decent armor, while still occupying the same space as a normal Dark Matter Reactor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17547</Index>
			<Text>Armored Dark Matter Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17548</Index>
			<Text>This Dark Matter Reactor has been enclosed in an armored shell, increasing durability at the cost of slightly less power. In the case of a reactor explosion, damage to nearby parts of the ship will be heavily reduced.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- linked dark matter  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17549</Index>
			<Text>Linked Dark Matter</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17550</Index>
			<Text>Until now, the idea of linking our dark matter reactors to harness more energy has been an impossible one. However, with recent revelations in dark matter theory, we have successfully devised a way to interconnect the spacial inhibitors containing our dark matter, greatly increasing their power efficiency.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17551</Index>
			<Text>Linked Dark Matter Reactor Set</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17552</Index>
			<Text>A state of the art series of 9 Dark Matter Reactors successfully bound together in an advanced protective lab. This facility features a powerful local shielding generator and several small robots that aid in ship repairs.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Dark Energy tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17553</Index>
			<Text>Dark Energy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17554</Index>
			<Text>Utilizing an incredibly complex series of warp fields, we can create a localized, massive void of energy, naturally filled in with constant amounts of dark energy. We can then harness this dark energy by collapsing the warp fields, yielding a substantial burst of power. A Dark Energy reactor repeats this process in quick succession, never allowing the dark energy to grow out of hand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17555</Index>
			<Text>Dark Energy Reactor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17556</Index>
			<Text>This Dark Energy Reactor produces vast amounts of energy. We can only construct a large version. Since the process of harnessing dark energy involves the constant inhibition of its expansion, compromising this system will lead to a catastrophic explosion. Energy and Beam weapons will not damage this reactor, however, owing to the energetic voids within.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Missile Point Defense tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17557</Index>
			<Text>Missile PD I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17558</Index>
			<Text>We can adapt our atmospheric missile point defense systems for space usage. It might prove useful for countering enemy missiles at a longer range than mass driver point defense systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17559</Index>
			<Text>Missile Point Defense - Light</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17560</Index>
			<Text>This small turret can launch very fast and agile missiles in a 360 degree field of fire, meant to counter enemy missiles at medium range. The missiles are primed to explode near the targeted enemy missiles, and though their damage is small, the explosive radius is very large. This turret uses a lot of ordnance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17561</Index>
			<Text>Missile PD II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17562</Index>
			<Text>As enemy missiles become more sophisticated, we can compensate by upgrading our Missile Point Defense systems to launch better counter missiles.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17563</Index>
			<Text>Missile Point Defense - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17564</Index>
			<Text>This larger Missile Point Defense turret launches heavier, but still very fast missiles to counter enemy missile attacks at long range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- mass driver_short description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17565</Index>
			<Text>Mass Driver - Long</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17566</Index>
			<Text>This version of the Mass Driver has a longer barrel, useful for ships with more space. Its projectiles have longer range and a larger explosive radius.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- subspace artillery II tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17567</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Artillery_II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17568</Index>
			<Text>We can develop larger versions of our current subspace artillery weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17569</Index>
			<Text>Dual Mass Driver - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17570</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer barrel version of the Smaller Dual mass cannon. It has more range and deals more damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17571</Index>
			<Text>Massive Cannon - Heavy</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17572</Index>
			<Text>Even more monstrous than the massive cannon, Only Battleships and Titans can mount this cannon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Disintegrator Array II tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17573</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17574</Index>
			<Text>We can now research and construct a larger disintegrator array.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17575</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17576</Index>
			<Text>This is a smaller array for our smaller ships. It does less damage, but requires less power to operate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17577</Index>
			<Text>Disintegrator Array - Large</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17578</Index>
			<Text>Enemy commanders will quake in fear at the sight of our new large Disintegrator arrays. These hulking weapons can only be fitted on Battleships or Titans, however.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fast shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17579</Index>
			<Text>Fast Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17580</Index>
			<Text>Since the recharge rate of our Class I Shields is rather low, we can invest research into a slightly stronger medium and small shield with a faster recharge rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17581</Index>
			<Text>Fast Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17582</Index>
			<Text>Since the recharge rate of our Class III Shields is rather low, we can attempt to research a slightly stronger large shield with a faster recharge rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17583</Index>
			<Text>Class I Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17584</Index>
			<Text>This medium shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It is also stronger than a regular class I medium shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power in hyperspace.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17585</Index>
			<Text>Class III Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17586</Index>
			<Text>This large shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It is also stronger than a regular class III large shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power in hyperspace.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Battle shields shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17587</Index>
			<Text>Battle Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17588</Index>
			<Text>We believe it would be possible to further improve our quickly recharging Class I Fast shields by making them a little stronger, and adding the ability to recharge during combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17589</Index>
			<Text>Battle Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17590</Index>
			<Text>We believe it would be possible to further improve our quickly recharging Class III Fast shields by making them a little stronger, and adding the ability to recharge during combat.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17591</Index>
			<Text>Class I Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17592</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It can also recharge during combat, and it is stronger than a regular Class I Fast shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17593</Index>
			<Text>Class III Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17594</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a very fast recharge rate, which takes some time to kick in after combat. It can also recharge during combat, and it is stronger than a regular Class III Fast shield. Unfortunately, it draws more power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17595</Index>
			<Text>Small Stations</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17596</Index>
			<Text>In order to defend our colonies from the growing danger of enemy fleets, we have recently devised blueprints to construct our first orbital station, a new type of structure that is larger than our small and heavy platforms. In addition, the creation of a long-range missile defense system was deemed imperative for our stations, and these weapons should prove effective against any comparatively long range enemy assaults.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Orbital Defense missile tech description -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>17597</Index>
			<Text>Light Orbital Missile Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17598</Index>
			<Text>This fixed-mount missile launcher fires salvos of long range missiles which are effective against a wide range of targets. It is only practical for stations, but can also be installed on our heavy platforms.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- fighter hangars 2 tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17599</Index>
			<Text>Bombers Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17600</Index>
			<Text>These hangars are very similar to standard fighter bays, but they can hold our heavy fighters and bombers, at the expense of longer spawn times.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17601</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Theory II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17602</Index>
			<Text>We can develop a Fighter bay which will be able to hold our larger fighter hulls and our bombers as well.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Anti-Matter bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17603</Index>
			<Text>This is a bomber dedicated Anti-Matter bomb bay. The bombs will inflict heavy, pure damage to slower moving enemy capital ships. This module fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Melt bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17604</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bays</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17605</Index>
			<Text>We can develop internal Melt bomb bays for our Bombers which would be very powerful versus shields, while also causing some EMP damage.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17606</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bays 3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17607</Index>
			<Text>Melt bombs deal high damage, are effective against shields, and cause some EMP damage. They are slightly more accurate and robust in comparison to other fighter bombs, but they are also slower. This module fires 3 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter shield bomb bays -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17608</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Shield Bomb</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17609</Index>
			<Text>We can develop internal shield-bomb bays for our bombers. These bombs were developed to counter ships that rely on shields as their only means of defense.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17610</Index>
			<Text>Shield-Bomb Bay 3</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17611</Index>
			<Text>Shield Bombs are specifically designed to counter enemies who only use shields to defend their ships. These bombs have a 75% chance to bypass shields and damage ship components, while delivering a small amount of EMP damage. They are not very effective against armor, however. This module fires 3 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17612</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17613</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17614</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Ion Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17615</Index>
			<Text>Ion Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17616</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Ion Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17617</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17618</Index>
			<Text>Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17619</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17620</Index>
			<Text>Anti Matter Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17621</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Anti-Matter Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17622</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17623</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 6</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17624</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Plasma Bomb Bay 4. It fires 6 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17625</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Bomb Bay 8</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17626</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Plasma Bomb Bay 4. It fires 8 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17627</Index>
			<Text>Melt Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17628</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Melt Bomb Bay 3. It fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17629</Index>
			<Text>Shield-Bomb Bay 4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17630</Index>
			<Text>This is a bigger version of the Shield-Bomb Bay 3. It fires 4 bombs per salvo.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Blue laser mk4  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17631</Index>
			<Text>Blue Laser Mk4</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17632</Index>
			<Text>These are truly high fire rate laser weapons. They also do more damage and require more power to maintain.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		<!-- Nano Storage short description - building -->
			<Index>17633</Index>
			<Text>+600 maximum goods storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Advanced Pulse Capacitor -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17634</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Pulse Capacitor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17635</Index>
			<Text>This is an improvement over the basic electromagnetic capacitor. Any ship equipped with pulse capacitors will be substantially more difficult to disable with electromagnetic pulse weaponry. They also aid the ship to recover faster from EMP overloads</Text>
        </Token>			
		<Token>
			<Index>17636</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Pulse Capacitor - Small</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17637</Index>
			<Text>This is an improvement over the small basic pulse capacitor, meant for ships with tight space. It is less efficient than the bigger version.</Text>
		</Token>	  
		<Token>
			<Index>17638</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Capacitors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17639</Index>
			<Text>Protecting our ships from EMP damage is becoming a necessity. We can design advanced, more efficient versions of our basic pulse capacitors.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- cold shields shields tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17640</Index>
			<Text>Cold Shielding I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17641</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct a very interesting Class I Shield variant. It is now almost fully resistant to Energy beams, accomplished by nullifying their temperature on impact. Hence the term, "Blue Shield". These shields recharge during combat, provide a large protection radius, and consume high amounts of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17642</Index>
			<Text>Cold Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17643</Index>
			<Text>We can now construct a very interesting Class III Shield variant. It is now almost fully resistant to Energy beams, accomplished by nullifying their temperature on impact. Hence the term, "Blue Shield". These shields recharge during combat, provide a large protection radius, and consume high amounts of power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17644</Index>
			<Text>Class I Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17645</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a high protection radius and is almost fully resistant to Energy Beams, yet also decently resistant to Energy Projectiles. It recharges during combat, but has a high power demand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17646</Index>
			<Text>Class III Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17647</Index>
			<Text>This shield has a high protection radius and is almost fully resistant to Energy Beams, yet also decently resistant to Energy Projectiles. It recharges during combat, but has a high power demand.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Auto Turret type 68 -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17648</Index>
			<Text>AutoTurret Type68</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17649</Index>
			<Text>This 3 barreled turret fires high explosive rounds and is a bit faster than the Type 80. It is also more armored.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Drone Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17650</Index>
			<Text>Drone AI Command</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17651</Index>
			<Text>Rather than depending on a living being, we can easily design an AI program to take control of a smaller drone fighter. This comes with multiple advantages, such as the elimination of life support systems, as well as greater capacity for acceleration and turning speed. These drones can be launched from a special tube able to be installed on larger ship hulls.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17652</Index>
			<Text>Basic Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17653</Index>
			<Text>This is our first Drone AI command module. It contains the hardware and software of an independent drone, as well as basic power generation and storage.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17654</Index>
			<Text>Improved Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17655</Index>
			<Text>After improving our knowledge in power generation techniques, we are now able to construct an improved command module that can generate and store twice the amount of earlier modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17656</Index>
			<Text>Shielded Drone Command Module</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17657</Index>
			<Text>This drone command module as a basic shield installed as well as an improved software, enabling it to track more than one target.</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17658</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Matter Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17659</Index>
			<Text>Drone Plasma Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17660</Index>
			<Text>Drone Ion Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17661</Index>
			<Text>This is a small bomb bay intended for a drone. Typically, it contains only 4 bombs, and the drone will need to resupply at its mothership after two or three bomb runs.</Text>
		</Token>												
		<Token>
			<Index>17662</Index>
			<Text>Drone Pulse Beam</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17663</Index>
			<Text>A pulse beam specifically modified for use on a drone. It is very accurate, but not as strong as its larger counterpart.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17664</Index>
			<Text>Drone Attack Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17665</Index>
			<Text>This attack cannon fires 5 rounds at high velocity in close range bursts. It has limited ammo, usually sufficient enough for a short skirmish.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17666</Index>
			<Text>Basic Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17667</Index>
			<Text>This Basic engine provides thrust and turn thrust for the drone. Drones can withstand much greater G-forces than if a living being were to be present. It is also equipped with a small secondary command unit that can track targets, should the main command module be destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17668</Index>
			<Text>Improved Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17669</Index>
			<Text>This improved engine provides more thrust, as well as some more power storage for the power hungry weapon modules.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17670</Index>
			<Text>Shielded Drone Engine</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17671</Index>
			<Text>This drone engine module provides a little less thrust than the improved engine module, but also comes fitted with a basic shield, providing increased survivability for the drone.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17672</Index>
			<Text>Drone Rocket Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17673</Index>
			<Text>This is a simple rocket launcher that can be fitted on a drone. It has less range than a standard rocket launcher.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17674</Index>
			<Text>Drone Launch Tube</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17675</Index>
			<Text>A tube used to launch a drone into combat. It is cheaper and smaller in comparison to fighter bays, as airlocks are not needed for the drone.</Text>
		</Token>			
		<!-- Nano Ordnance -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17676</Index>
			<Text>Small Nano Ordnance Locker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17677</Index>
			<Text>This Storage locker has been augmented with an army of small Nanobots that assemble the needed type of ammunition from raw materials. Within, ammunition is created in very small parts, allowing this locker to fit 4 times the ordnance of a normal ordnance pod. Drawbacks are higher production cost and a small explosion if the locker is destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>					
		<!-- Plasma vectoring -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17678</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17679</Index>
			<Text>We can accelerate the high-pressure system used to vent plasma from the ship's reactors. This can increase damage output by a high percentage. The density of the plasma will make it slightly more effective versus shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17680</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring III</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17681</Index>
			<Text>We can use calibrated reactor power to further narrow the focus of the plasma streams, making the plasma flame more destructive. This comes with a much higher power cost, but it is more effective against shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17682</Index>
			<Text>Plasma Vectoring IV</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17683</Index>
			<Text>Using more power and higher pressure systems leads to very focused and lethal plasma vents, at the expense of higher power and ordnance consumption.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17684</Index>
			<Text>High Pressure Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17685</Index>
			<Text>This plasma thrower uses a higher pressure vent system and increases the damage of the plasma cloud. It also fares well against shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17686</Index>
			<Text>Power Assisted Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17687</Index>
			<Text>This plasma thrower vents a more focused plasma cloud thanks to power transfer from the ship's reactors. It is very good versus Shields, but requires high power and more ordnance.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17688</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Plasma Thrower</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Advanced Fuel Cells tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17689</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Power Cells</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17690</Index>
			<Text>Advancements into new types battery technology allow us to manufacture higher capacity Power Cells.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17691</Index>
			<Text>Small Advanced Power Cell</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17692</Index>
			<Text>This Small Power Cell can store 50% more power than the basic one.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<Token>
			<Index>17693</Index>
			<Text>Medium Advanced Power Cell</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17694</Index>
			<Text>This Medium Power Cell can store 50% more power than the basic one.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Improved SRMs -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17695</Index>
			<Text>Improved SRM Systems</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17696</Index>
			<Text>We can further improve our short range missile technology by creating more destructive missiles, with additional range and utility.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17697</Index>
			<Text>Lightning Storm</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17698</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Shadow Storm, with more missiles per salvo, and increased damage per missile. However, they have a slightly lower chance to penetrate enemy shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17699</Index>
			<Text>Assault Orbital Missile</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17700</Index>
			<Text>Likely the longest range weapon ever created, This orbital missile emplacement will launch a barrage of devastatingly powerful and maneuverable missiles, designed to target frigates and larger ships. Missile carriers are launched which propel themselves to the target and separate into multiple fast and evasive rockets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17701</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Orbital Missile Launcher</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17702</Index>
			<Text>This orbital missile launcher fires large missiles which are designed to strike frigates and larger ships. It features an extremely long range, and a separation phase when missiles near the target.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Defensive structures description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17703</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Laser Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17704</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Heavy Laser Turret. It can target everything in a short planetary range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17705</Index>
			<Text>Fires Heavy Laser pulses. Short Range.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17706</Index>
			<Text>Disruptor Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17707</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Disruptor Turret. It has increased damage over the Heavy Laser Turret, but is too imprecise to target Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17708</Index>
			<Text>Fires Heavy Disruptor pulses. Cannot target Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17709</Index>
			<Text>Photon Cannon Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17710</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Photon Turret. Its major advantages are explosive projectiles and longer range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17711</Index>
			<Text>Fires Photon Charges. Medium range. Explosive payload.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17712</Index>
			<Text>System Defense Torpedo</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17713</Index>
			<Text>This planetary defense emplacement fires guided torpedoes over very long range. The torpedoes are huge and armored, thus physically resistant to point defense.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- plasma thrower blue  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17714</Index>
			<Text>Vast amounts of power is used to deliver a lethal plasma cloud which is also excellent versus shields. Sadly, with high power requirements and slightly less range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Extender snipers -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17715</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17716</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17717</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper AP Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17718</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper AP Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>		
				<Token>
			<Index>17719</Index>
			<Text>Extended Gauss Sniper HEAP Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17720</Index>
			<Text>This is a longer version of the Gauss Sniper HEAP Cannon. Mainly designed for Frigates and above, it has a longer range with higher damage. It requires more power to fire and maintain, as well as larger shells.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Forward shotguns -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17721</Index>
			<Text>Forward H.V.E Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17722</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the H.V.E Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17723</Index>
			<Text>Forward Repeater Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17724</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the Repeater Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17725</Index>
			<Text>Forward E.S Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17726</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the E.S Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17727</Index>
			<Text>Forward Dragons Breath Shotgun</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17728</Index>
			<Text>This is a forward facing version of the Dragon Breath Shotgun, designed for Fighter to Frigate roles. It has less range and a limited field of fire, but also lower cost and mass.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Rapid laser structures description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17729</Index>
			<Text>Rapid Laser Emplacement</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17730</Index>
			<Text>This is the planetary version of the Rapid Laser Cannon. It can target everything in a Medium planetary range and fires repeating bursts of laser pulses at a high rate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17731</Index>
			<Text>Fires Rapid Laser pulses. Medium Range.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Remnant  tech  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17732</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Heavy Laser</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17733</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17734</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Bridge</Text>
		</Token>										
		<Token>
			<Index>17735</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Energy PD</Text>
		</Token>												
		<!-- some buildings  description -->				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17736</Index>
		  <Text>Pirate Hidden Treasure</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17737</Index>
		  <Text>From Orbit, it appears as nothing out of the ordinary. However, your fleet commander insists these are the right coordinates, and ground troops should be sent to investigate.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17739</Index>
		  <Text>Friendly natives have been found living on this planet. They are very skilled workers and enjoy bartering for almost any of our trinkets. They offer friendship to the rulers of this planet. +1 production and +1 food per turn to the owner of this planet.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17740</Index>
		  <Text>+1 production and +1 food per turn</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17741</Index>
		  <Text>Native Village</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17742</Index>
		  <Text>Overdrive Capital Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17743</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced Capital Engines that provide 50% more thrust, but require double the power.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>17744</Index>
		  <Text>Overdrive Titan Engines</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17745</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced Titan Engines that provide 50% more thrust, but require double the power.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<!-- Cockpits description -->				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17746</Index>
		  <Text>Side By Side Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17747</Index>
		  <Text>This Cockpit allows for two pilots to sit side by side, with more integration between systems. It's slightly better than 2 separate cockpits.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
		  <Index>17748</Index>
		  <Text>Tandem Cockpit</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17749</Index>
		  <Text>This Cockpit allows for two pilots to sit one behind the other, with more integration between systems. It's slightly better than 2 separate cockpits.</Text>
		</Token>
        <!-- adv fighter shields  description -->						
		<Token>
			<Index>17750</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Shield Generator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17751</Index>
			<Text>A larger module with 2 linked shield generators provides over twice the shield power of a single shield generator, but also at the cost of more than twice the power supply.</Text>
		</Token>		
        <!-- drone cannons improved  description -->								
		<Token>
			<Index>17752</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti-Fighter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17753</Index>
			<Text>This drone cannon has an increased fire rate and a high chance to penetrate shields. It was designed as an anti-fighter weapon, as fighters often depend specifically on shields.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17754</Index>
			<Text>Drone Anti Ship Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17755</Index>
			<Text>This drone cannon is designed to cause large amounts of damage to armor by overcoming the armor's deflection characteristics.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17756</Index>
			<Text>Drone HEAP Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17757</Index>
			<Text>Although possessing a slightly lower fire rate than the repeater cannon, this drone cannon fires exploding, armor piercing rounds. The rounds are, however, less effective at armor penetration when compared to the AP cannon. The rounds also have a chance to penetrate shields.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Drone Ion beam  description -->				
		<Token>
			<Index>17758</Index>
			<Text>Drone Ion Pulse Beam</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17759</Index>
			<Text>An Ion pulse beam, specifically modified to fit within a drone. It is very accurate, but not as powerful as its bigger version.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fighter Battle and blue  description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17760</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Battle Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17761</Index>
			<Text>In order for our small crafts to survive battles with larger ships, they require better shields. These shields will recharge during combat, but they require more energy to maintain.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17762</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Cold Shields</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17763</Index>
			<Text>With the ability to recharge during combat, along with resistance to beam weaponry, these shields should noticeably improve the battle capabilities of our small crafts.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17764</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17765</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Fast Fighter Shield. It can recharge during combat, but it demands more power.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17766</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17767</Index>
			<Text>This Fighter Shield version is similar to the Fighter Battle Shield, but with high resistance to Energy and Beam weapons as well.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17768</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Battle Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17769</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Advanced Fighter Fast Shield. It can recharge during combat, but it demands more power.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17770</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Blue Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17771</Index>
			<Text>This Fighter Shield version is similar to the Advanced Fighter Battle Shield, but with high resistance to Energy and Beam weapons as well.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Xenocide tech  description -->				
		<Token>
			<Index>17772</Index>
			<Text>Xenocide I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17773</Index>
			<Text>Utilizing our knowledge of Xeno Genetics, along with our highly advanced computer networks, we can design a fearsome biological weapon.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17774</Index>
			<Text>Xenocide II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17775</Index>
			<Text>We can create an even deadlier biological bomb. Assuming we dont mind some... Experimenting. Retaining ethical treatment, we can conduct non life-threatening, temporary trials on test subjects. Be them prisoners of war... Volunteers... Or our own, unsuspecting citizens.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Mega cities and HD housing -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17776</Index>
			<Text>High Density Housing</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17777</Index>
			<Text>Special zones on the planet, specifically designed to house a large amount of the population while maintaining ordinary living standards. Our population will find them more than acceptable to live in.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17778</Index>
			<Text>Mega Cities</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17779</Index>
			<Text>Mega Cities are designed to house as much population as is comfortably possible, featuring automated technology to maintain optimal living conditions. It features buildings that rise high into the sky, and bridges interconnecting them. Due to the structure's massive size as well as the resources devoted to construction, large amounts of material must be removed from the surrounding soil, reducing fertility on the planet by a small amount.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17780</Index>
			<Text>This structure was specifically designed to house a large amount of the population while maintaining ordinary living standards. These zones can house 1 billion citizens.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17781</Index>
			<Text>+1 planet population, +25 storage</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17782</Index>
			<Text>Mega City</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17783</Index>
			<Text>A Mega City is a zone with high rise skyscrapers, dedicated to housing 2 Billion population in decent living conditions. Due to the loss of vast expanses of arable land, fertility is slightly reduced.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17784</Index>
			<Text> (-0.2) Fertility on build, +2 max population, +50 storage</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Massive laser and disruptor cannons -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17785</Index>
			<Text>Massive Disruptor Cannon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17786</Index>
			<Text>This is the largest Disruptor cannon we can usefully mount on a spaceship. These Dual cannons can disrupt more efficiently, making them more effective against shields. They also have a better chance to completely penetrate shields.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17787</Index>
			<Text>Massive Laser Cannon Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17788</Index>
			<Text>A bigger version of the Heavy Laser Turret. It can pack quite a punch, increasing its effectiveness versus armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17789</Index>
			<Text>Massive Polaron Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17790</Index>
			<Text>Massive Polaron Cannons mounted on a turret platform with advanced cooling systems for rapid and sustained fire. Bypasses shields.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- more drone bombs  description -->			
		<Token>
			<Index>17791</Index>
			<Text>Drone Shield Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17792</Index>
			<Text>Drone Cluster Bomb Bay</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17793</Index>
			<Text>This is a unique bomb module for drones. It contains 8 miniature fusion bombs designed to strike capital ships. The drone can fire them all in a single bomb run.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- stations -->			
		<Token>
			<Index>17794</Index>
			<Text>Battle Stations</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17795</Index>
			<Text>The need to defend our colonies against enemy invasion grows constantly. Our engineers have designed a substantially large battle station that will bolster the defensive prowess of our more important planets. We have also iterated upon our orbital missile launchers, a step toward nullifying the threat of long range enemy weapons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17796</Index>
			<Text>Sector Stations</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17797</Index>
			<Text>These hugely massive stations are larger than most titans, and will serve our planets tremendously against almost any threat. Advancements in missile technology have also lead us to an ingenious new orbital missile defense weapon, perfectly suited to combat any large invasion fleet, no matter their range.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17798</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Projectors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17799</Index>
			<Text>Subspace Projectors greatly speed up stardrive speeds for ships within their influence. We can use them as "fast lanes" in our empire. They also have a very large sensor coverage and can be used for spying near enemy borders. Orbital Platforms are also our first step into the colony orbital defense path. These small orbitals, when grouped together, can fend off entire small invasion fleets.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- Phased Rapid Energy Cannons -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17800</Index>
			<Text>Gravitons</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		<!-- Massive Photon Turret -->
			<Index>17801</Index>
			<Text>For decades, our scientists have understood and been able to utilize the quantum forces of the graviton particle, in applications such as gravitational plating and warp travel. Now, with our newfound mastery over it, we have been able to devise an incredibly powerful weapon.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17802</Index>
			<Text>Massive Photon Turret</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17803</Index>
			<Text>Massive Photon Cannons mounted on a turret platform. These bigger cannons fire larger Photon torpedoes.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17804</Index>
			<Text>Improved Phased Rapid Energy Turret</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17805</Index>
			<Text>This turret will unleash rapid fire energy projectiles that will penetrate whatever shields the enemy may have, along with doing twice the damage to armor. It has a medium to long range.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- 4x4 beam  turret tech  description -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17806</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Fusion Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17807</Index>
			<Text>Fusion particle beams gain increased damage over laser beams, but are much less efficient. This particular model is mounted on a swivel to achieve a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17808</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Phasor Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17809</Index>
			<Text>The Heavy Phasor Beam Turret provides a devastating dual Phasor beam with a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17810</Index>
			<Text>Heavy Laser Beam Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17811</Index>
			<Text>The Heavy Laser Beam Turret provides a dual Laser beam with a 120 degree field of fire.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- shape memory -->					
		<Token>
			<Index>17812</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Small</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17813</Index>
			<Text>A more advanced version of the initial Shape Memory Technology. Mass is unchanged.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17814</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Small</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17815</Index>
			<Text>The most advanced Shape Memory Internal bulkhead we currently possess. It can withstand powerful internal explosions.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17816</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17817</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead II Large</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17818</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Medium</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17819</Index>
			<Text>ShapeMemory Bulkhead III Large</Text>
		</Token>		
        <!-- Metal internal bulkheads -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>17820</Index>
			<Text>Improved Internal Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17821</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Original Internal Bulkhead. It is more durable and resists explosions.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17822</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Internal Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17823</Index>
			<Text>This is a more advanced version of the Improved Internal Bulkhead. It is even more durable and has better explosive resistance.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17824</Index>
			<Text>Improved Reinforced Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17825</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Original Reinforced Bulkhead. It is more durable and resists explosions.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17826</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Reinforced Bulkhead</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17827</Index>
			<Text>This is a more advanced version of the Improved Reinforced Bulkhead. It is even more durable and has better explosive resistance.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Armor Piercing Tech -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17828</Index>
			<Text>Armor Piercing II</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17829</Index>
			<Text>Armor Piercing III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17830</Index>
			<Text>Ballistic and Missile weapons will pass through the first Medium sized armor (or 2 small) module encountered. The armor will take no damage.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17831</Index>
			<Text>Ballistic and Missile weapons will pass through the first Large sized armor (or 3 small) module encountered. The armor will take no damage.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- fighter Rockets -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17832</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Rockets I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17833</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Rockets II</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17834</Index>
			<Text>Rockets are unguided, fast projectiles with high payloads stored in pods.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17835</Index>
			<Text>Increased sized and damage Rocket pod technology.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17836</Index>
			<Text>Hydra Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17837</Index>
			<Text>Talon Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17838</Index>
			<Text>Hydra rocket pods are very small, able to be mounted on most of our smallest ships. They fire a barrage of quick moving rockets which deal slightly extra damage towards armor.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17839</Index>
			<Text>Talon Rockets are an improvement over the Hydra Rockets. The pod is slightly larger, has higher range, and deals more damage. In addition, they are very effective against armor.</Text>
		</Token>	
 		<!-- Armored Defense -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17840</Index>
			<Text>Reactive HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17841</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Reactive Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17842</Index>
			<Text>Ceramic HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17843</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Ceramic Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17844</Index>
			<Text>Composite HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17845</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Composite Alloys Armor plate for added durability. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17846</Index>
			<Text>Crystal HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17847</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Crystal Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17848</Index>
			<Text>Hyper Active HMG Defense Turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17849</Index>
			<Text>A Heavy Machine Gun turret mounted on a Hyper Active Armor plate for added durability. An effective weapon against fighters and missiles. It has 60% of the strength and 75% Deflection of the non weapon Armor plate.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<!-- Class V and VII shields -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17850</Index>
			<Text>Class V Shield</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17851</Index>
			<Text>Class VII Shield</Text>
		</Token>
				<Token>
			<Index>17852</Index>
			<Text>This is a massive shield for its size, with more protection range and more shielding</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17853</Index>
			<Text>Armored Heavy Shielding II</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17854</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve the output of our Class V shields, along with adding Composite Alloy armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17855</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Canopy Shield</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17856</Index>
			<Text>The best Canopy Shield Generator we can safely install on a starship.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17857</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Canopy Shields</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17858</Index>
			<Text>It is now possible to improve the output of our Canopy shields, along with adding Active Armor plates around them for more protection.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Medium Nano Ordnance -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17859</Index>
			<Text>Nano Ordnance Locker</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17860</Index>
			<Text>A larger version of our small nano ordnance locker. The larger space means fewer walls, making it more efficient. It holds more ordnance than 4 smaller nano lockers, but produces a dangerous localized explosion if destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Home Defense -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17861</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17862</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 4 Home Defense Fighters</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17863</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 4 Fighters that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Fighters available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17864</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17865</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 16 Home Defense Fighters</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17866</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 16 Fighters that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Fighters available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17867</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17868</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 3 Home Defense Corvettes</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17869</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 3 Corvettes that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Corvettes available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17870</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17871</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 9 Home Defense Corvettes</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17872</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 9 Corvettes that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Corvettes available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17873</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Defense Squadron</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17874</Index>
			<Text>A squadron of 2 Home Defense Frigates</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17875</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a squadron of 2 Frigates that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Frigates available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
			<Index>17876</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Defense Wing</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17877</Index>
			<Text>A wing of 4 Home Defense Frigates</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17878</Index>
			<Text>This facility will support a wing of 4 Frigates that will leap into the colony's defense when an enemy is spotted. It will launch the best Frigates available in your empire. You will be able to control them only in battle. They cost Money to Launch, but you get it back if they make it back home.</Text>
		</Token>
	    <!-- money description -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17879</Index>
			<Text>+1.25 credit per colonist</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Laser Beams -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17880</Index>
			<Text>Laser Beams</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17881</Index>
			<Text>A laser is a device that emits light through a process of optical amplification based on the stimulated emission of electromagnetic radiation. The term "laser" originated as an acronym for "light amplification by stimulated emission of radiation". A laser differs from other sources of light in that it emits light coherently. Spatial coherence allows a laser to be focused to a tight spot, which with enough power, can be a deadly weapon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Remnant Fighter Shield -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17882</Index>
			<Text>Remnant Fighter Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17883</Index>
			<Text>An Advanced shield used by Remnant Fighters.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Fast Fighter shields -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17884</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17885</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Standard Fighter Shield. It has a much faster recharge rate, but it needs more time before recharge starts.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17886</Index>
			<Text>Advanced Fighter Fast Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17887</Index>
			<Text>This is an improved version of the Advanced Fighter Shield. After a decently long cool down, it can recharge very quickly.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Module HP bonus -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17888</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 5% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17889</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 10% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17890</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 15% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17891</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 20% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17892</Index>
			<Text>Provides a 25% hit point bonus to all ship modules.</Text>
		</Token>	
		<!-- Environment Preferences Description-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17893</Index> <!-- Opteris -->
		  <Text> prosper in Barren worlds, and like Ice, Steppe and Tundra worlds. They dislike Oceanic, Swamp and Desert Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17894</Index> <!-- Vulfar -->
		  <Text> prosper in Ice worlds, and like Tundra, Steppe, and Terran worlds. They dislike Desert, Barren and Swamp Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17895</Index> <!-- Ralyeh -->
		  <Text> prosper in Oceanic worlds, and like Terran, Steppe and Swamp worlds. They dislike Barren and Desert Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17896</Index> <!-- Pollops -->
		  <Text> prosper in Swamp worlds, and like Terran, Oceanic, Steppe and Tundra worlds. They dislike Barren, Ice and Desert Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17897</Index> <!-- Draylok -->
		  <Text> prosper in Desert worlds, and like Swamp, Steppe oceanic and Terran worlds. They dislike Barren, ice and Tundra Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17898</Index> <!-- Cordrazine -->
		  <Text> prosper in Steppe worlds, and like Desert and Ice, worlds. They dislike Barren, Swamp and Oceanic Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17899</Index> <!-- Kulrathi -->
		  <Text> prosper in Tundra worlds, and like Ice, Terran worlds. They dislike Barren, Desert and Swamp Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17900</Index> <!-- Humans -->
		  <Text> prosper in Terran worlds, and like Steppe and Swamp worlds. They dislike barren, Ice and Desert Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- weapons and event weapons -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17901</Index> 
		  <Text>Prototype energy beam weapon</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17902</Index> 
		  <Text>This is our first attempt in creating reliable energy beam weapon, it is crude, but should be effective.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17903</Index> 
		  <Text>Advanced Flak Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17904</Index> 
		  <Text>Using an improved type of barrel and loading mechanism, Advanced flak cannons improve range, velocity and damage over the previous versions.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17905</Index> 
		  <Text>Advanced Dual Flak Turret</Text>
		</Token>				
		<Token>
		  <Index>17906</Index> 
		  <Text>This is our first attempt in creating reliable energy beam weapon, it is crude, but should be effective.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>17907</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>With the introduction of new technologies, our efforts in the creation of a powerful beam have been made successful. We managed to create some new experimental phasor weapons, but since we do not fully understand our discovery, these weapons are not perfectly optimized.</Text>

		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17908</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Dual Phasors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17909</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Dual Phasors are our first venture into the creation a dual beam weapon. Unfortunately, the inherent instability of the powerful dual beams limits their maximum range.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17910</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Experimental Phasor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17911</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Early Phasor prototype, its pure destructive power usually comes with the price of increased size. As a side effect, the extended length of this beam weapon has increased its maximum range, and also mysteriously amplified its mass repulsion effect.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- S_cannon -->
        <Token>
		  <Index>17912</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>S cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17913</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Supersonic Stabilized Cannon enhanced with our newest autoloader systems.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17914</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The Supersonic Stabilized Cannon shoots projectiles at very high velocity. It also features impressive reload times.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- RAD -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17915</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Rotating Atom Destroyer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17916</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>An Energy gatling weapon. Designed to continuously rotate massive barrel heads to prevent overheating from rapid fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17917</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>R.A.D. can shoot in rapid succession, so long as the ship can provide the needed power.</Text>
		</Token>
        <!-- ScrappyBeam --> 
		<Token>
		  <Index>17918</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>ScrappyBeam.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17919</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This antiquated beam weapon design was previously abandoned due to its lower overall damage potential.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17920</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This weapon may not initially appear impressive when considering the weak damage potential, but as it turns out, it's very good at damaging shields and disrupting onboard power flow.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Energizer3x3 -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17921</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Energizer.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17922</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A giant single beam system mounted on a turret.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17923</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The unique design of this large beam system gives it an interesting side effect. Thanks to more densely packed particles within the magnetized stream, there is a slight lock-on effect when multiplying the mass of the target, making tracking more precise.</Text>

		</Token>
		<!-- RemnantNuker -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17924</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>RemnantNuker.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17925</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A compact weapon of mass destruction.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17926</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>For a missile of this size, it's a strikingly devastating weapon. Not only does it melt armor, but it also emits a deadly EMP blast.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Magnetrom -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17927</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Magnetrom</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17928</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A weapon designed around its energized missile warhead.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17929</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The sole purpose of the Magnetrom is to swiftly destroy enemy shields, thereby overloading the vulnerable ship's electronics and massively draining any stored power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- TritaniumMissiles-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17930</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Tritanium Missiles</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17931</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Missiles constructed from an incredibly durable material.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17932</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Tritanium Missiles are a straightforward weapon. A missile that can receive massive amounts of damage, yet still deliver its payload to the target.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Enforcer -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17933</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Enforcer</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17934</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A highly advanced Kinetic weapon that uses energy to propel the shells.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17935</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The Enforcer is a rapid fire weapon system. It requires both power and ordnance to shoot.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Cyclone -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17936</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Cyclone</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17937</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A prototype weapon, created in an effort to bridge the gap between energy and ordnance based cannons.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17938</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Cyclone represents the worst and best of both worlds. It features high projectile speeds, great damage, extensive range, and a low cool down, but it requires substantial amounts of power and ordnance to fire.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- AtomizingBattery -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17939</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Atomizing Battery</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17940</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A heavy artillery energy cannon.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17941</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A weapon specifically designed to support long range engagements, providing firepower from the back lines.</Text>

		</Token>
		<!-- Black matter weaponry-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17942</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Dark Matter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17943</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>This ingenious weapon utilizes Dark Matter as a projectile. The process to confine and stabilize such a force was made successful by transferring small amounts of Dark Matter from our collectors, then wrapping them into their own individualized charges that can be loaded into a projectile chamber. Upon impact, they release their devastating power.</Text>

		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17944</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The most compact Dark Matter cannon. A fixed position cannon that fires small bursts of stabilized Dark Matter. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17945</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Dark Matter turret. Fires in semi-rapid succession. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17946</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Heavy Dark Matter turret with an expanded field of fire coverage. Features a burst weapon firing system. Doesn't require ordnance or power to fire. Produces small yield explosion when destroyed.</Text>
		</Token>
	    <Token>
		  <Index>17947</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Light Dark Matter Cannon</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17948</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Dark Matter turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17949</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Heavy Dark Matter turret</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- StorageShield -->
		<Token>
		  <Index>17950</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Integrated Storage Shield</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17951</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A Shield module with integrated capacitors for better efficiency.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17952</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>The integration of capacitors into this shield module has yielded an improvement in shield strength. Provides a small additional benefit of storing some ship-wide power.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- AncientArmor -->
         <Token>
		  <Index>17953</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Ancient Armors</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17954</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Small Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17955</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Medium Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token> 
		   <Token>
		  <Index>17956</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Large Ancient Armor</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17957</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>A very durable piece of Ancient Armor. Can be used both as an internal bulkhead, or as external armor.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>17958</Index> <!-- Secret -->
		  <Text>Ancient armor is covered in a gold-like coating. Each armor module is made of smaller pieces that tear off when struck.</Text>
		</Token> 
		<Token>
			<Index>17959</Index>
			<Text>Abandoned Warehouse</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17960</Index>
			<Text>Your ship detected an abandoned warehouse on the surface, send troops to investigate.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<!-- Underhive -->
		<Token>
			<Index>17961</Index>
			<Text>Shady places are perfect ground to gamble. With right connections we can make a profit.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17962</Index>
			<Text>Having slaves is such an convenient labour force, sadly we need to feed them as well.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17963</Index>
			<Text>Underhive</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17964</Index>
			<Text>The underhive is the most run-down city on the planet where most of the rules are created by Corsair gangs. It is a difficult place to live where the power has long been turned off. People rule through fear and shun the rich that live in the capital.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17965</Index>
			<Text>You can't stop the underhive, and the smugglers keep profiting from it.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17966</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Computing II</Text>
		</Token>			
		<Token>
			<Index>17967</Index>
			<Text>Xeno Computing III</Text>
		</Token>					
		<Token>
			<Index>17968</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons I</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17969</Index>
			<Text>Due to the small size of our platforms, the creation of compact orbital weapons now seems to be a necessity. Such weapons would be able to fire in all directions, but as a result we will only be able to install them on our small and heavy platforms. They will feature a high range 360 degree field of fire, and will be armed with kinetic projectile rounds.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17970</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons II</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17971</Index>
			<Text>With advancements in weapons technology, we can develop an improved version of our previous platform kinetic cannons. This Mk2 Orbital Kinetic Cannon will fire faster rounds, have an even higher range, and deal more damage than its predecessor.</Text>
		</Token>						
		<Token>
			<Index>17972</Index>
			<Text>Platform Weapons III</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17973</Index>
			<Text>With the success of our previous platform cannons, our engineers have determined that the best path forward in platform weaponry would be the creation of a high-powered, extremely compact cannon. It will deal even more damage, have an incredibly high range, and even higher projectile speed. The longer reload time should make it worth it.</Text>
		</Token>								
		<Token>
			<Index>17997</Index>
			<Text>Clean World</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>17998</Index>
			<Text>In peaceful times, our people had no need for massive factories. Steady growth and a clean environment were always our way of life. +1 homeworld fertility</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>17999</Index>
			<Text>+0.5 credits per colonist</Text>
		</Token>				
		<!-- hulls tech description -->		
		<Token>
			<Index>18000</Index>
			<Text>Drone</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
			<Index>18001</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18002</Index>
			<Text>Our first fighter hull provides the basic needs of the military. However, in order to expand our tactical options, we can invest time and research into the designing of another, larger fighter hull.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18003</Index>
			<Text>Fighter Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18004</Index>
			<Text>We can develop yet another fighter hull, designed to be used as a heavy fighter.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18005</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18006</Index>
			<Text>Our first Corvette hull was a success. We can now design a heavier, larger corvette hull that will add more diversity to our ship arsenal.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18007</Index>
			<Text>Corvette Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18008</Index>
			<Text>Furthering the diversity of our Corvette hulls can help us overcome future military challenges.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18009</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18010</Index>
			<Text>We can research a new frigate hull. It may be an extension of our current frigate hull, or even a brand new design. Regardless, it will have more potential.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18011</Index>
			<Text>Frigate Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18012</Index>
			<Text>Frigates can play a major part in a fleet. They can even be launched from a carrier ship, assuming the carrier is large enough. We can design an upgrade, or a brand new frigate hull to further increase our combat options.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18013</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18014</Index>
			<Text>Cruisers are the backbone of any fleet. It is recommended that we research heavier cruiser types in order to keep up with the military's demands.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18015</Index>
			<Text>Cruiser Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18016</Index>
			<Text>In order to strengthen our core fleets, we believe developing another, heavier cruiser design would be a good decision.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18017</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18018</Index>
			<Text>We can design a larger Battleship to command and coordinate our fleets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18019</Index>
			<Text>Battleship Hulls II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18020</Index>
			<Text>A larger Battleship, almost as big as a Titan, can be researched and introduced into the war effort.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18021</Index>
			<Text>Titan Hulls I</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18022</Index>
			<Text>We can now design the marvel of our empire. This ship design is around twice the size of the first Titan we have designed. This Super Titan will proudly represent the height of our Empire's military might. The production cost of these ships is so high that building one would be a massive undertaking. Building too many might be an unwise decision.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18023</Index>
			<Text>Assault Cannons II</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18024</Index>
			<Text>Most advanced type of space battery, 2 enormous barrels providing firepower to bring down biggest of ships.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18025</Index>
			<Text>Assault Disintegrator</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
			<Index>18026</Index>
			<Text>The damage output of these monstrosities can overwhelm any enemy ship, as well as their own ship's power reserves.</Text>
		</Token>
		<Token>
		  <Index>18027</Index> <!-- Dauntless preferred envs -->
		  <Text> prosper in Terran worlds, and like Steppe and Tundra and Ice worlds. They dislike Barren, Desert Swamp amd Oceanic Worlds.</Text>
		</Token>		
		<Token>
		  <Index>18028</Index>
		  <Text>New line of rocket pods build upon very effective Talon class rockets.</Text>
		</Token>
		<!-- Hellstorm systems-->
        <Token>
		  <Index>18030</Index>
		  <Text>Advanced SRM Systems</Text>
		</Token>
        <Token>
		  <Index>18031</Index>
		  <Text>This is the top of the line in short range missile systems, using the newest technologies in missile structures to improve their utility, range, and most importantly, damage.</Text>
		</Token>
        <Token>
		  <Index>18032</Index>
		  <Text>Hell Storm</Text>
		</Token>
        <!-- Venom pods-->
		<Token>
		  <Index>18033</Index>
		  <Text>Venom Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
        <Token>
		  <Index>18034</Index>
		  <Text>This Venom pod is an improvement over the Talon pod in that it fires more missiles per attack, at only slightly lower damage per missile. They also have a slight chance to penetrate enemy shields.</Text>
		</Token>
        <!-- Nemesis pods-->
        <Token>
		  <Index>18035</Index>
		  <Text>Nemesis Rocket Pod</Text>
		</Token>
        <Token>
		  <Index>18036</Index>
		  <Text>With this extremely deadly rocket pod, we are now able to launch missiles that deal twice the normal damage to armor. Their chance to penetrate shields is also increased.</Text>
		</Token>		
	</TokenList>
</LocalizationFile>
