<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>Discover Crashed Ship</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Unknown defenders</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Before reaching the Crashed Ship, your troops were attacked by unknown enemies and had to fall back, the crashed ship takes off and warps out of the system.</DescriptionText>
       <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Skeleton</string>
        <string>Skeleton</string>
      </TroopsToSpawn>     
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>4</Chance>
      <TitleText>A unique technology and great peril!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find the pillar, inside on they found a data core with schematics of unknown technology. After removing the data core from the socket, the pillar shakes and crumbles to rubble alarming a dormant Remnant Inhibitor!</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <UnlockTech>Cyclone</UnlockTech>	  
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Remnant Inhibitor</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>	  
      <TroopsToSpawn>
      </TroopsToSpawn>	  
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>4</Chance>
      <TitleText>A unique technology!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the area, your troops find the pillar, inside on they found a data core with schematics of unknown technology. After removing the data core from the socket, the pillar shakes and crumbles to rubble alarming dormant space defenders.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <UnlockTech>Energizer3x3</UnlockTech>	  
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Heavy Drone</string>
		<string>Xeno Fighter</string>
		<string>Xeno Fighter</string>
		<string>Xeno Fighter</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>	  
      <TroopsToSpawn>
      </TroopsToSpawn>	  
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Red Alert</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While your troops carefully examine the wreckage and the still intact computer systems, one of them trips an alarm. Your troops manage to deactivate the alarm and salvage the control system which is valuable on the black market, however a fleet of Remnant vessels jumps into orbit detecting your presence.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>500</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Xeno Fighter</string>
        <string>Heavy Drone</string>
        <string>Heavy Drone</string>
      </RemnantShipsToSpawn>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>24</Chance>
      <TitleText>A sad wreck</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of what is clearly a very, very ancient shipwreck. Time and nature have taken their toll on the wreckage. Even so, there are some curiosities among the wreckage that will have some value on the open market.</DescriptionText>
      <MoneyGranted>250</MoneyGranted>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Excellent find</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Here you have made an excellent discovery - what appeared from orbit to be a shipwreck was in fact not a wreck at all but a completely intact alien light frigate! What's more, it appears to be space worthy and inside of its cargo there's mysterious artifact.</DescriptionText>
      <FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Heavy Drone</string>
		<string>Heavy Drone</string>
		<string>Support Drone</string>
      </FriendlyShipsToSpawn>
      <GrantArtifact>true</GrantArtifact>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>10</Chance>
      <TitleText>Unstable</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of what is clearly a very, very ancient shipwreck. Time and nature have taken their toll on the wreckage. Even so, scans showed its reactor is still working and by minute emitting more and more antimatter particles. Your forces were evacuated in haste. Soon after the reactor explodes destroying the wreckage and severely damaging the planet</DescriptionText>
      <NumTilesToMakeUnhabitable>3</NumTilesToMakeUnhabitable>
      <ChangeBaseFertility>-0.6</ChangeBaseFertility>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>2</Chance>
      <TitleText>Space car?</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>Your forces examine the wreckage of a small space craft that crashed into planet long time ago. From the description or wreckage and scans its too small for a spaceship, even more puzzling is that it has wheels. But it cant be a car, they never were designed to be a spacecrafts.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
  </PotentialOutcomes>
</ExplorationEvent>