<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>LifeForms</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>35</Chance>
      <TitleText>Ghost town!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops approach the settlement, they immediately notice the whole town is in ruin. No signs of the original inhabitants remain, and now only the occasional pack of antlions roams this ghost town. Following procedure, they remove all the threats and continue on.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Abandoned Town</ReplaceWith>
      <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
		<string>Antlion</string>
		<string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
	  </TroopsToSpawn>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>35</Chance>
      <TitleText>Pirates!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>From far away your troops notice a pillar of smoke coming from the settlement. As they get closer, it becomes clear that the village suffered from an attack not long ago. Most of the buildings were turned to rubble. All inhabitants now dead from gunshot wounds. This was the work of pirates! They must still be somewhere close.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <PirateShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Corsair</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
      </PirateShipsToSpawn>
      <ReplaceWith>Destroyed Village</ReplaceWith>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>25</Chance>
      <TitleText>Cant communicate</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops approach the settlement, they see what appear to be some very primitive structures. Upon trying to make first contact with the inhabitants, the only result was fearful growling and screeching. Any form of communication here has failed. Better leave them alone.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Native Village</ReplaceWith>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Primitive tribe!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops approach the settlement, they're noticed by one of the primitive villagers. Through sheer determination and diplomatic trust, they establish a basic way of communication. After negotiating, a mutual agreement was made wherein they will provide us with a workforce so long as we provide them with food.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Friendly Native Village</ReplaceWith>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Small primitive town!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>You troops noticed that this town was surrounded by a large number of mines. Going against procedure and navigating the minefield to enter the settlement, they were met with quite the uproar of curiosity. They easily established a way of communicating. A deal was struck with the town elder wherein they will provide us with a workforce in exchange for few of our scientists to educate their people.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Primitive Small town</ReplaceWith>
      <ChangeRichness>-0.2</ChangeRichness>
    </Outcome>
    
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Pirate colony!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As soon as they stepped foot into this town, your troops were met with a cold and affixed gaze from each of the people working around. Eventually, what seems to be a leader of sorts approaches your troops, explaining that this is in fact a slave colony... Run by pirates. If we free them from their imprisonment, they will provide us with a strong workforce, but they still need to be fed and given some basic materials to allow the town to grow and prosper.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Primitive Medium town</ReplaceWith>
      <PirateShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Corsair</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
      </PirateShipsToSpawn>
    </Outcome>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Large town!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>When your troops first entered this town, it looked abandoned, with not a single soul in sight. After investigating for signs of life, it turns out the inhabitants are in fact a very small and weak humanoid species, but they're highly intelligent. They're willing to work on our research projects in return for us providing them food, materials, and a physically larger workforce.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <ReplaceWith>Primitive Large town</ReplaceWith>
    </Outcome>
    
  </PotentialOutcomes>
 </ExplorationEvent>