<ExplorationEvent>
  <Name>Temple</Name>
  <PotentialOutcomes>

    <Outcome>
      <Chance>15</Chance>
      <TitleText>Transaction</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops move to enter the Temple, they met a scavenger named Yuriy who was using very strange dialect that had to be translated, apparently he has found and old relic inside of the temple and is willing to sell it for the right price!</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <MoneyGranted>-250</MoneyGranted>
      <GrantArtifact>true</GrantArtifact>
    </Outcome>
     <Outcome>
      <Chance>30</Chance>
      <TitleText>It's an alien nest!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>As your troops approach the temple, they hear sounds coming from inside. Unfortunately, a nest of antlions has made its home here! In a attempt of clearing the alien colony inside, they rigged explosives into the temple entrance. The detonation shook the structure, causing it to collapse.</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <TroopsToSpawn>
        <string>Antlion</string>
		<string>Antlion</string>
		<string>Antlion</string>
        <string>Antlion</string>
	</TroopsToSpawn>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>25</Chance>
      <TitleText>Remnant worshipers!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While mapping interiors of the temple you troops noticed a lot of primitive sculptures and scribbles in the walls worshiping some kind of god's that came to them from heavens. While examining the top level of the temple, they couldnt find a match in any records of ancient pyramids with the oddly large and flat and empty top level, which was resembling and landing pad. Suddenly they hear a sonic boom, and above their heads a remnant ship appeared, hovering for a minute charging its warp drive. Your troop fall back in haste, as soon they left the temple the ship takes off, creating a powerful shock wave destroying the temple. .</DescriptionText>
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
      <RemnantShipsToSpawn>
        <string>Ancient Frigate</string>
       </RemnantShipsToSpawn>
    </Outcome>
     <Outcome>
      <Chance>5</Chance>
      <TitleText>A unique technology!</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>After Scouting the interior of the temple, your troops located an hidden chamber, inside on they found a data core with schematics of unknown technology. After removing the data core from the socket, the whole structure starts to shake and after you troops evacuate it crubles to rubble.</DescriptionText>
      <UnlockTech>AncientArmor</UnlockTech>	  
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>3</Chance>
      <TitleText></TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>From outside the enormous pyramid like structure resembles and old temple, but after inspecting it from inside you troops reported what it is instead is a huge living complex.</DescriptionText>
      <ReplaceWith>Ancient megacity</ReplaceWith>	  
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>6</Chance>
      <TitleText>Rob or Ben?</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the Temple your troops detected a energy source coming from deep inside of the structure. When they were closing in to the source, they started to hear weird noises, like two individuals arguing. They entered a huge room, there was no one there, at the center of it they saw a pyramid shaped structure that was clearly a high tech, centuries old. Suddenly they heard a voice coming from the structure. The structure was a sentient Ai, sent by ancient Race to guide primitive races. Sadly it was misunderstood by them, taking it for a god. They build a temple around it and isolated it from everyone deep inside. The civilisation perished, but the ai was left behind. After centuries, it developed a split personality to have a company. Now they argue who was the prime, Rob or Ben? The Ai asked if it can tap into our research networks for siphoning new knowledge in return increase the effectiveness of tax. </DescriptionText>
      <ReplaceWith>Ai</ReplaceWith>	  
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
    <Outcome>
      <Chance>20</Chance>
      <TitleText>Scavenger pirates</TitleText>
      <DescriptionText>While exploring the Temple your troops stumbled upon a group of scavengers, that immediately start firing. We dealt with them with no losses, but they werent alone. Thy were a part of a space pirates crew, that noticed that something had happen. Soon after several ships launched from the surface. </DescriptionText>
       <PirateShipsToSpawn>
		<string>Corsair</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
		<string>Corsair-Fighter-Mk2</string>
      </PirateShipsToSpawn>	 
      <RemoveTrigger>true</RemoveTrigger>
    </Outcome>
  </PotentialOutcomes>
 </ExplorationEvent>