<DiplomacyDialog>
  <Dialogs>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>First Contact</DialogType>
      <Friendly>Hmph... You dont look so weak, alien. Kinda remind me of my pet deathhorn. I think we'll get along just fine.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Another abomination... Prowling the galaxy, trying to waste my time with pointless greetings. Pathetic.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>What did you just call yourselves? PLURAL, was it? Disgusting creatures. Get out of my sight.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Colonized Warning</DialogType>
      <Friendly>Took the TARSYS system right out from under our noses! Well played, PLURAL, but stupid nonetheless.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Taking TARSYS wasn't a bright idea, SING. But looking into your eyes, I can tell that you aren't exactly the brightest of creatures. I'll put this simply so the likes of you can understand... There won't be a next time.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>Spreading into the TARSYS system like the vermin you are. Keep it up, scum... We'll start the extermination soon enough.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Aggression Warning</DialogType>
      <Friendly>Hah! Your silly toy weapons just managed to scratch the paint from one of our ships! What's wrong, you don't like the color of death?</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Oh, what's that? You destroyed one of our ships? Impressive. But do you know what would be even more impressive, SING? A hundred ships hovering over your homeworld... Dropping nukes.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>What a pathetic display of such meager strength. Like an insect buzzing around, just begging to be squished.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Warning Ships</DialogType>
      <Friendly>What's that pile of rust doing in our space, SING? Get it out before we start to care.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>I wonder how much the wrecked versions of your ships are worth? Being in our space and all, we could try to find out. There's gonna be a lot of trash floating around here soon.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>You'd better start praying to whatever gods you worship, SING. Let's hope they can pull your ships out of our space before we turn them all into space trash.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Warning Ships then Colonized</DialogType>
      <Friendly>We're amused by your bold move, SING. But that amusement won't last long. Our people took you for an enlightened form of life. TARSYS was our world. Don't steal from us again.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Puny SING... Gambling with your own pathetic excuses for lives. You may have placed your bets on the TARSYS system, but we're the ones dealing the cards. And I've gotta say, the odds of SING guts being spilt are quite high.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>You dare spread your filth onto a planet that WE had already claimed?! The rot of your kind will sink into the planet's soil when we rightfully reclaim what you have stolen.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Warning Colonized then Ships</DialogType>
      <Friendly>SING, what do you think you're doing with those buckets of rust you call space ships? Get them out of the TARSYS system before you end up doing something you'll regret.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Let this serve as a message to SING maggot command. Your cowardly actions are beginning to annoy us. If you don't want us to get our hands all nice and bloody, you'll stop colonizing our space.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>You've stolen the TARSYS system from OUR space! You taint the galaxy with your filth, and your meager existence!One of these days... We'll slaughter your people. Mark my words.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War</DialogType>
      <misc1>Everything you own... It's ours now.</misc1>
      <misc2>Your worlds will burn. Your people will weep. We'll paint our ships with your blood, all before you finally submit. This galaxy will bow to the might of the Dauntless.</misc2>>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Dunno_Anybody</DialogType>
      <Default>We've already conquered every meager foe we've found. They acted just the same as you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Greeting</DialogType>
      <Friendly>Urgh... More talking?</Friendly>
      <Neutral>What do you want from us, SING.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>Make it quick, maggot. I don't exactly like to chat.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Racial_Inquiry_1</DialogType>
      <Default>Hold on, let me adjust this stupid thing.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Racial_Response_1</DialogType>
      <Default>What? I can see you just fine.
      </Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AboutUS</DialogType>
      <DL_Agg>I'll tell you this, SING. This galaxy is ours for the taking, and that's exactly what we plan to do. Stay out of our way. </DL_Agg>
      <DL_Hon>You don't even want to know what we've been through. Pray that you will never suffer as we did.</DL_Hon>
      <DL_Pac>We've swam our way through a torrent of strife and suffering. And we'll do it all over again if we have to.</DL_Pac>
      <DL_Ruth>We have a duty, SING, to dominate those who will bend their knee, and to exterminate those who will not.</DL_Ruth>
      <DL_Cunn>Any bastard can shoot down a ship. No... We know how to bring down an empire. We've done it many times before, and we'll do it again.</DL_Cunn>
      <DL_Xeno>Stop talking. We know not to trust others, SING, and we know not to trust you.</DL_Xeno>
      <DL_Exp>This galaxy is ours for the taking. It's as simple as that.</DL_Exp>
      <DL_Tech>We're smart bastards, SING. You see all this Metal sticking out of me? I drilled it in myself.</DL_Tech>
      <DL_Mil>Our might shines above all the rest. This is not something that is debatable.</DL_Mil>
      <DL_Ind>We've filled planets with factories before. Doesn't work out in the long run. Still worth it though.</DL_Ind>
      <DL_Gen>We do what we want, as it comes. Life's just more simple that way.</DL_Gen>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_InsufficientTrust</DialogType>
      <Default>And how am I to know that you'll follow up on your end of this deal? Nice try, SING. You can't trick us.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_AcceptGreatOffer_LowTrust</DialogType>
      <Default>Hmph... Hand it over and get out of my sight.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Reject_PoorOffer_LowTrust</DialogType>
      <Default>This is absurd. We will not deal in petty dirt with such maggots as yourselves.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Reject_PoorOffer_EnoughTrust</DialogType>
      <Default>Interesting. You've got my attention, but we need more.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Reject_Insulting</DialogType>
      <Default>Is that it, SING? Pathetic.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Fair</DialogType>
      <Default>That'll do. Now hand it over and get out of here.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Good</DialogType>
      <Default>Not too bad, SING. We'll take it. Looks like you can be of use after all.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Great</DialogType>
      <Default>Hmph... Really? Well then, you've gained our favor on this day, SING. Keep it up.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Gift</DialogType>
      <Default>Haha... Paying your tribute. It seems you've learned your place, SING. We'll remember this.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Fair_Pleading</DialogType>
      <Default>Ergh... Take your bounty and leave.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_InsufficientFear</DialogType>
      <Default>Maggots... We'd rather die or kill you than accept these terms.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Fair_Threatening</DialogType>
      <Default>Brave of yourselves to make such threats. Regardless, we accept.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OfferResponse_Accept_Bad_Threatening</DialogType>
      <Default>The Dauntless will remember this day, SING. And so too will your people as they bleed out on the ground.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>WarDeclared_FeelsBetrayed</DialogType>
      <Default>Clever, PLURAL. I would've done the same thing in your place. Let's get this over with.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>WarDeclared_Generic</DialogType>
      <Default>The Dauntless are no strangers to war, SING. When you realize your mistake, you will beg us for forgiveness.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Greeting_AtWar</DialogType>
      <Default>What do you want? Here to beg for mercy?</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War Defense</DialogType>
      <Default>We're at war now, SING. Stay the hell out of our space. You had your chances.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War BC</DialogType>
      <Default>You should've shown more respect, SING. Regardless, your time is now at its end. We will destroy you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War BC TarSys</DialogType>
      <Default>Do you think we truly cared about that insignificant little TARSYS system? Why settle for that when we can simply enslave every last one of your worlds? The answer, to us, was obvious. Prepare to die, SING.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Offer NAPact</DialogType>
      <Default>Don't attack us, and we won't attack you. I'd really urge you to accept this arrangement, SING. For your own sake.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>NAPact Accepted</DialogType>
      <Default>You've made a wise decision today. Now just go back to whatever you were doing.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>NAPact Rejected</DialogType>
      <Default>No? Well now, that's just disappointing. And here I thought you were one of the smart ones. You'll see what happens to those who disobey us.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Offer Trade</DialogType>
      <Default>Wanna buy some of our useless junk? I'm sure you wouldn't mind picking through it. I suppose that is what you do, isn't it?</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Trade Accepted</DialogType>
      <Default>Smart choice. Good luck finding anything valuable in that junk. We'll be taking our cut of the profits, by the way.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Trade Rejected</DialogType>
      <Default>You won't even take the scraps from our plates, will you? Admirable, yet foolish.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ComeAround_NAPACT</DialogType>
      <Default>Hah, it's okay to come crawling back, maggot. We knew you would.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ComeAround_TRADE</DialogType>
      <Default>So now our junk is valuable to you? Well, you could've just said so. Good luck scrounging through all that trash.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Xeno Demand Tech</DialogType>
      <Default>Ergh... Give us TECH_DEMAND, alien. The sight of you is like poison to my cybernetic eyes.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Xeno Demand Tech Accepted</DialogType>
      <Default>A wise decision, avoiding our wrath. We'll let you know when we need something else.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Xeno Demand Tech Rejected</DialogType>
      <Default>Foolish. There are many dangers in this galaxy, SING. You'll soon learn why we needed that technology.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Insult Military</DialogType>
      <Default>Pathetic, weak creatures.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Compliment Military</DialogType>
      <Default>An impressive display of might, PLURAL. That's something we respect.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Compliment Military Better</DialogType>
      <Default>Where once we observed a pathetic excuse for a military, we now see much more potential. Maybe one day, you might be of use to us, PLURAL.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War Imperialism</DialogType>
      <Default>You have some fine worlds, maggots... Worlds that are ours now. We'll be destroying your ships on our way in. Make way for your new rulers.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Kulrathi</DialogType>
      <Default>Those bears... They value might, as do we.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Kulrathi</DialogType>
      <Default>Those... Creatures. Their favor of culture over prowess is what clouds their judgement. Maybe one day they'll learn.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Kulrathi</DialogType>
      <Default>Disgusting beasts. In ancient times, we hunted similar beings to extinction on our world. They tasted foul. Kulrathi meat, though? Exquisite. Even my deathhorn enjoys it.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Pollops</DialogType>
      <Default>Haha, those pathetic little plants. We've taken many things from them, and they just keep giving! I'd leave them alone if you know what's good for you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Pollops</DialogType>
      <Default>We barely even know what those plant things are. Do they have brains? Might be fun to use 'em for target practice.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Pollops</DialogType>
      <Default>Tried feeding one to my deathhorn once. He spat it out...</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Vulfen</DialogType>
      <Default>The Vulfen... Now there's a race that understands brutality. Somethin' strange about em though... They shave their fur and act like humans sometimes. Called "hurries" if I remember right.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Vulfen</DialogType>
      <Default>Just another race yet to be subjected to our whims. I have nothing else to say about them.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Vulfen</DialogType>
      <Default>We can smell their stink all the way from our own ships during battle! They claim to value strength, but they're among the weakest in this galaxy. What a pathetic excuse for a civilization.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Cordrazine</DialogType>
      <Default>Takes guts to domineer and entire race of innocent little things. Don't know what the little guys are called, but they do good work. Helped build some parts for this ship, actually.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Cordrazine</DialogType>
      <Default>Are those the little furballs or the things that hang from the ceiling? Pathetic creatures, either way.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Cordrazine</DialogType>
      <Default>They think they're powerful for enslaving a bunch of useless little furballs?! We'll show them what true domination looks like when they're chained up in our cargo holds! And we'll take those little furballs, too!</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Ralyeh</DialogType>
      <Default>Disturbing as they are, we've found them to be respectable. They exert their power through religious conversion. Unusual, but obviously effective.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Ralyeh</DialogType>
      <Default>That's the race the humans are so obsessed with drawing, isn't it? Hmph, art... Useless waste of time. Other than that, we know nothing of those Ralyeh.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Ralyeh</DialogType>
      <Default>Our people revolted against our gods long ago. Yet the Ralyeh enslaved themselves to theirs. Pathetic.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War Imperialism Break NA</DialogType>
      <Default>Remember our non-aggression pact? Now that you've kindly colonized so many worlds... We're here to collect on our end of that agreement. Surrender now, PLURAL.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Conquered_Player</DialogType>
      <Default>Yet another worthless race, conquered by the Dauntless. You'll make useful slaves, PLURAL.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Offer Open Borders</DialogType>
      <Default>It's a dangerous galaxy, SING. Ever thought about the benefit of having some more powerful ships flying through your systems? In exchange, you could fly through ours as well. Not that you have any reason to come over here.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Open Borders Accepted</DialogType>
      <Default>Wonderful. You won't regret this... I promise.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Open Borders Rejected</DialogType>
      <Default>You'll regret this, SING. You could've used our protection.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Invaded NA Pact</DialogType>
      <Default>Treason... The ultimate backstab. I always suspected this might happen, and alas, it has. You'll regret this decision, SING.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Invaded Start War</DialogType>
      <Default>And here I thought we were getting along just fine. But apparently not... When you're a slave, you'll remember the mistake you just made.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Opteris</DialogType>
      <Default>There's something enrapturing about a being that cannot feel. Completely devoid of what makes life... Worth living. Just an utter void that observes, calculates, and kills. The ultimate psycopaths.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Opteris</DialogType>
      <Default>Computers with limbs. Nothing we can enslave, but interesting nonetheless. Useless to us, though. So long as they stay away from our systems.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Opteris</DialogType>
      <Default>One day, we'll destroy every last one of those mechanical maggots. We'll program them to finally know pain, and damn will they know it...</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Claim System</DialogType>
      <Friendly>TARSYS is ours. If there's enough room for both of us in this galaxy, then surely you can respect that.</Friendly>
      <Neutral>Stay away from the TARSYS system.</Neutral>
      <Hostile>You'd better tell that useless hunk of rust to fly right back where it came from, SING. If you take TARSYS, you'll be paying with your lives.</Hostile>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Stole Claim</DialogType>
      <Default>You damned alien maggots! We'll torch every last one of your planets for stealing TARSYS! ARRGH!</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_JustMetUs</DialogType>
      <Default>We don't know you. This talk is uselesss. No more questions, maggot.</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_NoProblems</DialogType>
      <Default>Could be better... Could be worse. We'll see what becomes of you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Problems</DialogType>
      <Default>Your kind annoy us, SING. Bad things happen to those who dare stand in our way.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_JustTerritorial</DialogType>
      <Default>Be relieved that we have only one issue with you, SING. Respect our claims and our territory, and there will be no bloodshed. Disrespect that wish, and you will know true pain.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_Territorial</DialogType>
      <Default>You have no respect for your betters. Our territory is ours. Our claims are ours. Do you understand, maggot?</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_AlsoMilitary</DialogType>
      <Default>The size of your military is as well a concern. We respect a proud display of strength, but this is just absurd.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_AlsoMilitaryWeak</DialogType>
      <Default>Your ships are weak as well, SING. And few in number. A dangerous truth in such a dangerous galaxy.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_MilitaryWeak</DialogType>
      <Default>Your fleets are small and weak, SING. You should care more about your safety... Especially from us.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_PrimaryMilitary</DialogType>
      <Default>The only thing we care about is that damned military of yours. We respect a proud display of strength, but this is simply absurd.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_AlliedWithEnemy</DialogType>
      <Default>Your alliance with TAREMP is pathetic. End it. </Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Problem_AlsoAlliedWithEnemy</DialogType>
      <Default>And come to think of it, you should end your alliance with TAREMP. Trust us, you don't want to be friends with them.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_NothingMajor</DialogType>
      <Default>Don't think we have any big problems to worry about yet, SING. Might not be allies, but we ain't enemies.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AtWar_Winning</DialogType>
      <Default>Come crawling back to your new masters? Here to ask for forgiveness? Don't worry, it won't matter soon enough. You were always meant to be slaves.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AtWar_Losing</DialogType>
      <Default>Your relentless nature is a soothing sight to see, SING. Many of our people have proudly given their lives to destroy you. When this is all over, we'll have our revenge.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>HelpUS_War</DialogType>
      <Default>Join us in our war with TAREMP. I promise you, it will be glorious. We'll divide the slaves evenly. First to take a planet keeps it.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>HelpUS_War_Yes</DialogType>
      <Default>Hah... I thought you'd agree. That blood hungry smile of your tells me everything I need to know. Let's get to the fight then, shall we?</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>HelpUS_War_No</DialogType>
      <Default>You dare stand in the way of our war? You'll regret this, SING.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Positive_Draylok</DialogType>
      <Default>Formidable creatures, the Draylok. Not sure if they are what they say they are, but their appearance doesn't matter to us. Their ships are strong, and their pride even stronger. There are many qualities within them that we see in ourselves.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Neutral_Draylok</DialogType>
      <Default>A devious people, but harmless to us. So long as it stays that way, we have no problem with them. Their worlds are all deserts, and our people hate the heat.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Opinion_Negative_Draylok</DialogType>
      <Default>Those imbeciles can't even fix their own holomasking technology. What use could they possibly be to us other than as slaves?</Default>
    </DialogLine>



    <!--  Second Run Localization Efforts -->

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Declare War Defense BrokenNA</DialogType>
      <Default>We were the ones who were supposed to violate that worthless peace pact! Clever move, PLURAL, clever move...</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_FAIR</DialogType>
      <Default>We can both see the futility in this war, SING. We must end it now, before it is too late.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_FAIR_WINNING</DialogType>
      <Default>Submit, maggot. Be thankful that we do not wish to destroy you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_EVENLY_MATCHED</DialogType>
      <Default>The longer this way goes on, the more both our of people will die. Do you want that, SING? Do you want that blood on your hands? You've proven yourself. Now end this.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_PLEADING</DialogType>
      <Default>Give us peace, or take our lives swiftly, coward.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_LOSINGBC</DialogType>
      <Default>We're above this, you and I. Some meager territory surely isn't worth the combined might of our militaries, is it?</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_WINNINGBC</DialogType>
      <Default>We have what we want now. Sign this treaty, and we'll go back to being ruthlessly upset.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_REJECTED</DialogType>
      <Default>An unfortunate response. History will forever remember the horrors we shall now commit.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFERPEACE_ACCEPTED</DialogType>
      <Default>Wise. We'll call off our assault. Be thankful this didn't get any bloodier, SING.</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ACCEPT_OFFER_PEACE</DialogType>
      <Default>Fair enough, I suppose... We'll have peace.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>REJECT_OFFER_PEACE_POOROFFER</DialogType>
      <Default>What an absurb plea from a maggot begging for its worthless life. Keep begging, tiny creature. It's amusing.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>REJECT_OFFER_PEACE_UNWILLING_BC</DialogType>
      <Default>There will be no peace! We will keep our worlds and retain our claims until the end of this war, do you hear me?!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ACCEPT_OFFER_PEACE_RELUCTANT</DialogType>
      <Default>Hmph... For the good of my people, I suppose that'll have to do.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>PROBLEM_RECENTWAR</DialogType>
      <Default>Enough of your musings, SING! My pet deathhorn died in our recent war. He was a loyal creature, and I'll never forget him!</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFER_ALLIANCE</DialogType>
      <Default>Listen to me now, SING. Have you considered just how powerful we could be if we pledged to fight alongside each other? It would be glorious!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ALLIANCE_ACCEPTED</DialogType>
      <Default>Haha! I knew you would agree! Then let us know each other as brothers at arms, SING. We will rightfully claim everything we are due, and this galaxy will bend its knee to our combined might!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ALLIANCE_REJECTED</DialogType>
      <Default>What a shame, SING. This is a dangerous galaxy, one that could've been ripe for our picking. Your loss.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>OFFER_ALLIANCE_TOO_COMPLICATED</DialogType>
      <Default>I don't have to time to weigh all these prospects! Get rid of the other conditions, then perhaps we'll consider your alliance.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AI_ALLIANCE_ACCEPT</DialogType>
      <Default>Haha! For you, SING, I would gladly torch our enemies together, rather than at odds. They will feel our combined wrath, and our newly forged might!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AI_ALLIANCE_REJECT</DialogType>
      <Default>An alliance? Pitiful. We have no reason to make such a pact.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>REJECT_PEACE_RUTHLESS</DialogType>
      <Default>Never! Your people will meet their death at our hands, SING! Your worlds will burn and your people will suffer!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>ACCEPT_PEACE_COLDWAR</DialogType>
      <Default>Hmph... No more bloodshed, huh? These terms are too beneficial for us to pass up. You'll have your peace, for now...</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>HelpUS_War_No_BreakAlliance</DialogType>
      <Default>Although we may not understand what it ever meant, we now know enough to end this alliance. Farewell, worm.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Stole Claim 2</DialogType>
      <Default>TARSYS was ours. Soon, PLURAL will understand what a lost world truly means.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Stole Claim 3</DialogType>
      <Default>Death is on the horizon, SING. Our claims, our worlds. I will not repeat myself again.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Caught_Spying_1</DialogType>
      <Default>Spying... Weak and pathetic. If you think you're brave enough, come take our secrets yourself. You won't like what you see.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Caught_Spying_2</DialogType>
       <Default>Do you have any idea what's gonna happen if you keep spying on us? Go ahead, keep it up. I dare you.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Caught_Spying_3</DialogType>
      <Default>All of our treaties are done with. All bets are off. Good luck, SING. Hope the spies were worth it.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Killed_Spy_1</DialogType>
      <Default>We killed your guy. Fed him to my pet deathhorn. Go ahead, try it again. He's still hungry.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Caught_Spying_Ally_1</DialogType>
      <Default>Cut it with the spies, SING. This alliance is a fragile thing, ain't it? You're lucky we don't call it off right now.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Caught_Spying_Ally_2</DialogType>
      <Default>Did you really think you could just spy on us, SING? Did you think we wouldn't do anything about it? Well guess again. We're done.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Offer Open Borders Friends</DialogType>
      <Default>Us being pals and all that, how about we let our ships pass wherever they please? You won't regret it, I promise.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Open Borders Friends Rejected</DialogType>
      <Default>You should learn what good things are, SING. Guess we'll just stick to our own space for now.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_JustMet</DialogType>
      <Default>You've got a lot of guts to ask for such a thing, SING. You just pop up on our viewscreens one day and now you're pretending we're all friends? Get out of my sight.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_NoAlliance</DialogType>
      <Default>Careful what you wish for. If you think you can take us in as friends, we're gonna need an alliance first, SING.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_AllianceTooYoung</DialogType>
      <Default>Are you kidding me? Friendship doesn't exactly come naturally for us, SING. You're lucky you got this far. Give it some time before pushing it, else this whole thing's off.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_WeAreTooStrong</DialogType>
      <Default>You're weak, SING. Maybe one day, when you're all grown up. Until then, keep dreaming.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_Accept</DialogType>
      <Default>Hell yeah! We're gonna screw up this universe, you and me. This whooole place is ours for the taking now, you hear?! Let's do this!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_Quest_DestroyEnemy</DialogType>
      <Default>I'm gonna make you an offer, us being friends and all. Why don't you go and annihilate those worms, the TAREMP. If you can do that, maybe then we'll talk.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_YouDidIt_KilledEnemy</DialogType>
      <Default>Well damn, son. You did it. With TAREMP out of the picture, I think we can finally team up. Hope this doesn't mean we can't still rough each other up every so often.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_RelationsPoor</DialogType>
      <Default>Hmph... Yeah right. Stop wasting my time, worm.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_Quest_AllyFriend</DialogType>
      <Default>You know, I think that'd be just dandy. One problem, though. You've gotta end your war with TAREMP and make 'em your allies. If you can do that, maybe we can be true buddies after all.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>Federation_YouDidIt_AllyFriend</DialogType>
      <Default>Well well, you finally did it. Now that you and TAREMP are friends, I think we can all get along just fine. You know, I think I'm gonna like this federation. I just hope you don't mind if we can still beat each other up some times.</Default>
    </DialogLine>

    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_YouAreNotAtWar</DialogType>
      <Default>How about you start showing some of your own damn guts before asking others to spill theirs? Pathetic.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_WeAreAtWar</DialogType>
      <Default>Can't you see with your own eyes?! We've been at war with TAREMP this whole damn time! Wake up!</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_Allied_OK</DialogType>
      <Default>Hell yeah, SING. We can fight 'em together. That filth is gonna regret ever crossing our paths. All of their worlds, all of their technology. That's just all ours for the taking, now.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_Allied_DECLINE</DialogType>
      <Default>You know, we might be some harsh bastards, but we don't betray our own damn allies. TAREMP's gonna love hearing about this.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_Reject_PoorRelations</DialogType>
      <Default>You think we'd do that for you? Hah... What a dream. How about you go back where you came from, worm.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_Reject_Pacifist</DialogType>
      <Default>We don't want anything to do with that. Things are better for us than you might realize, and we ain't about to mess that up.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_Reject_TooDangerous</DialogType>
      <Default>You think we stand a damn chance against them? Think again, pal.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>JoinWar_OK</DialogType>
      <Default>Hell, we're aching to stretch our muscles. For some tough asses like you, I think we can mess some stuff up. Let's do this.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
	
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>REJECT_OFFER_PEACE_ALLIED_WITH_ENEMY</DialogType>
      <Default>No, "friend", we will not sign peace while you are allied with our enemies.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>AI_ALLIANCE_REJECT_ALLIED_WITH_ENEMY</DialogType>
      <Default>Ah, looking for new friends, aren't you? Well, no. You are allied with our enemies. Break alliance with them and we shall see.</Default>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <DialogType>CUTTING_DEALS_WITH_ENEMY</DialogType>
      <Default>I'll be damned, you go to our enemies and sign treaties with them. We are friends, you know.</Default>
      <DL_Agg>Our alliance deal is off.</DL_Agg>
      <DL_Ruth>You are not worthy of any relations. Good bye.</DL_Ruth>
      <DL_Xeno>We are not going to have any agreements with you, jerks. Everything if off!</DL_Xeno>
      <DL_Cunn>Interseting plot revealed, mmm?</DL_Cunn>
      <DL_Pac>Nice. But next time, work with our allies, not our enemies.</DL_Pac>
      <DL_Hon>We will not tolerate this! Relations off, war on.</DL_Hon>
    </DialogLine>
    <DialogLine>
      <Default>I'll be damned, you crawl to our enemies and try to sign treaties with them regardless of our alliance!?</Default>
      <DL_Agg>Our alliance deal is off.</DL_Agg>
      <DL_Ruth>You are not worthy of any relations. Good bye.</DL_Ruth>
      <DL_Xeno>We are not going to have any agreements with you, jerks. Everything if off!</DL_Xeno>
      <DL_Cunn>Interseting plot revealed, mmm?</DL_Cunn>
      <DL_Pac>Nice. But next time, work with our allies, not our enemies.</DL_Pac>
      <DL_Hon>We will not tolerate this! Relations off, war on.</DL_Hon>
    </DialogLine>	
  </Dialogs>
</DiplomacyDialog>
